0000000001	Medvedev, aided by 34 unforced errors from Opelka, became the first Russian to win a Canadian trophy since Marat Safin 21 years ago.
0000000002	Throughout Ladakh, rock carvings are visible along pilgrimage and trade routes, and at wayside shrines.
0000000003	Some of these date to the Palaeolithic and Neolithic periods, others are more recent carvings.
0000000004	Their delineations include simple figures, animals and outlines of structures to more intricate works of more monumental and religious stature.
0000000005	Rock art continued to have an important place in Ladakh, with early sculptures dating from the eighth century onwards.
0000000006	In modern times, as the pace of development work escalates, especially along the routes and paths where these petroglyphs and rock art are located, many sites have been damaged and destroyed.
0000000007	Archaeologists and local stakeholders are taking up the task to conserve this heritage through interventions at the individual as well as government levels.
0000000008	This module focuses on the petroglyphs and rock art practices of Ladakh, the location and range of different types of petroglyphs and rock carvings, and symbolic significance.
0000000009	It also looks at other forms of prehistoric rock art, their links to trade and influence from outside the region.
0000000010	Finally, focusing on their current status and the preservation and recognition of petroglyphs and rock art as an important cultural heritage of Ladakh.
0000000011	These injuries should be examined for those who present with pain after a latest increase in activity with limited rest. 
0000000012	Ahead of Independence Day 2021, a survey has found that 39 per cent of Indian millennials find financial freedom to be the most liberating.
0000000013	The survey found that 65 per cent Indians on the dating app preferred freedom over money while 35 per cent chose money.
0000000014	Besides, 73 per cent users agreed that they are independent individuals who speak, think and support themselves on their own.
0000000015	With regard to relationships, 68 per cent users said they strongly believed in allowing their partners freedom.
0000000016	About 73 per cent said they wanted independent bank accounts to enjoy financial freedom in the relationship.
0000000017	Compared to this, 27 per cent users said they would not mind having a joint bank account with their partner.
0000000018	The survey also asked users about the importance of freedom of religion and the press.
0000000019	On the dating app, 90 per cent of the users felt that freedom of the press is important.
0000000020	And 76 per cent users said there should be laws to protect freedom of religion.
0000000021	An NFT, or a nonfungible token, is a digital file created using blockchain computer code.
0000000022	It is bought using cryptocurrency such as Ether or Wax and exists as a unique file unable to be duplicated, often just to be admired digitally.
0000000023	Regular exercise, even performed in areas with polluted air, may lower the risk of death from natural causes, according to a study published on Monday.
0000000024	The researchers wanted to understand the effects of regular exercise and long-term exposure to fine particle matter on the risk of death from natural causes.
0000000025	The researchers found that a high level of habitual exercise and a low level of exposure to air pollution was associated with lower risk of death from natural causes.
0000000026	On the other hand, a low level of habitual exercise and a high level of exposure was associated with higher risk of death, according to the researchers.
0000000027	“Further studies in areas with more severe air pollution are required to examine the applicability of our findings,” the authors wrote in the study.
0000000028	“People should not be forced to choose between physical activity and air pollution,” they said.
0000000029	Addressing both major public health issues through synergistic, upstream, system-level approaches would lead to long-term health benefits for humans and the planet, they added.
0000000030	A person who has body dysmorphic disorder (BDD) perceives defect in their body which otherwise is not there.
0000000031	This preoccupation is what gives them anxiety, distress, sleep problems and may also drastically impact social life, Dr Parikh states.
0000000032	No matter what size you are, no matter what number you are on the scale, you will always find fault with yourself.
0000000033	This clouds self-judgement, often leading to low self-esteem and body image issues, which are also symptoms of BDD.
0000000034	According to Dr Reddy, while social media does not directly cause BDD, it can act as a “trigger in those already genetically predisposed to the disorder”. 
0000000035	But perhaps strangest of all, the grapefruit hides a deadly secret. For some people, drinking just one glass of grapefruit juice could have shocking consequences.
0000000036	The bottom of the handi is layered with bay leaf and the chicken and rice is cooked on top of that.
0000000037	Locally known as the donne biryani, this dish is a soft, juicy and flavourful one. 
0000000038	From the coast of Tamil Nadu, comes this flavourful delight that is quite simple to make and will leave you wanting for more.
0000000039	While the pandemic has made people conscious about remaining active for health, fitness and immunity, doctors have noticed a significant rise in the number of people experiencing ‘stress fracture’. 
0000000040	From far down south comes this fairly simple biryani recipe sure to be a hit whenever you make it, it's called Kozikodan Biryani.
0000000041	Garnished with boiled eggs and chicken cooked in butter, this flavourful delicacy will surely lave you wanting for more.
0000000042	The vast landscape of Indian food covers much more than just these biryani recipes and there are many more dishes yet to be explored.
0000000043	Papads are one of our favourite things to munch on with tea, dal rice or just as they are - and the street-style papads top the list.
0000000044	Indian street snacks are spicy, crunchy and pack a punch of flavour, they are made with the simplest ingredients but manage to give us some of the best gastronomical experiences.
0000000045	Like those very crispy and crunchy sabudana papads that you find on the streets, which are the perfect munching companions with tea, dal rice or just as they are.
0000000046	With just the simple flavours of jeera and salt, these papads are addictively binge-worthy and you just won't be able to stop at one.
0000000047	The process is pretty simple and you can easily make and store these at home for weeks to come. Sabudana and jeera are found in all Indian households
0000000048	In the Divine Comedy, Dante goes down the circles of Hell meeting the world’s most illustrious sinners. 
0000000049	Soak sabudana overnight, next day boil them with jeera and salt. You can add extra jeera, dhaniya powder and even chillies to this. 
0000000050	Scoop out a spoonful and spread on parchment paper, let this sundry for 2-3 days, deep fry in hot oil and your sabudana papad is ready to be munched on.
0000000051	While the desire to look “good” is natural, the problem arises when one begins to evaluate self-worth through physical appearance. 
0000000052	When certain benefits, incentives, and decisions are skewed based on external appearances, they will surely disturb the social order.
0000000053	While people of any age can have BDD, it is commonly seen in the younger generation. It can also impact school children. 
0000000054	Time-consuming thoughts about appearance make it difficult to focus on schoolwork, and it can lead to students failing tests and having trouble concentrating.
0000000055	While the monsoons are enjoyed by many, the season also brings with it bacterial and viral infections because of the change in weather and the rise in humidity.
0000000056	Kanchan Naikawadi, managing director and preventive healthcare specialist at Indus Health Plus says in the monsoon season, the eyes get affected.
0000000057	Naikawadi shares some easy precautions which one can take during monsoon for good eye care.
0000000058	Always keep face towels, napkins, handkerchiefs, any cloth that you bring near your eyes and your hands clean.
0000000059	They prevent the eyes from making contact with any foreign substance and infectious agents like viruses and bacteria.
0000000060	Wash your eyes with cold water daily. Don’t rub your eyes harshly after waking up or removing contact lenses as that can permanently damage the cornea.
0000000061	They can cause extreme dryness in the eyes and can result in redness and irritation. Keep your glasses clean and dry.
0000000062	They contain a lot of viruses, bacteria and fungus that can transfer and cause harm.
0000000063	“Infections that generally happen during the rainy season are not just scary but pretty harmful, too,” says Naikawadi.
0000000064	It is the irritation or inflammation of the whites of our eyes. It is extremely contagious and spreads through even the littlest of contact.
0000000065	Although the infection goes away in a couple of days, it is necessary to keep your eyes covered.
0000000066	An infection when a red painful lump forms near the edge of the eyelid that may look like a boil or a pimple.
0000000067	Styes are filled with pus and can sometimes form on the inner part of the eyelid, too.
0000000068	A stye will start to disappear on its own in a couple of days but applying warm washcloth regularly will help with the pain and discomfort. 
0000000069	It is an open sore on the cornea and results in pus discharge, severe pain and blurriness of vision.
0000000070	It is a severe infection that can result in loss of vision and permanent blindness if not treated properly.
0000000071	According to experts, since the phased unlocking last year, cases of stress fracture have increased by 100 per cent. 
0000000072	Here, we listed 6 different egg curry recipes from across India - each of which will leave drooling with is unique flavour and aroma.
0000000073	Dim-er kosha is a Bengali style egg curry that tastes quite similar to the popular mangsho kosha also known as Bengali-style chicken or mutton curry.
0000000074	Eggs, boiled and fried and smeared in thick gravy made with onion, tomato, ginger-garlic and spices- this dish tastes the best when paired with basanti pulao.
0000000075	An egg-y version of North Indian butter chicken and paneer makhani, this dish wins hearts with its creamy and flavourful gravy. Pair it with roti or naan and relish.
0000000076	Goa has more to it than the pristine beachscape. One such factor that needs exploration is its cuisine.
0000000077	Each dish here is loaded with local spices, leaving a strong impression on your mind and palate. 
0000000078	Goan egg curry is a tangy recipe prepared with coconut cream, tamarind and poppy seeds.
0000000079	If you have tried Chettinad chicken, then Chettinad Egg Curry will surely leave you slurping.
0000000080	The Chettinad Egg Curry is a hard-boiled egg, cooked in Chettinad-style masala, this South Indian delicacy is a must try.
0000000081	Malvani cuisine is a standard cuisine of South Konkan region of India, Malvani food is an amalgamation of Goan and Maharastrian cooking styles.
0000000082	Each dish in this cuisine sees extensive usage of herbs and spices - one such example being Malvani egg curry.
0000000083	If you thought Hyderabadi cuisine is just about biryani, then you are in for a surprise. We agree biryani defines the food culture, but it's just the tip of the iceberg.
0000000084	If you dig in deep, you will find a pool of recipes that will blow your mind with its flavours and aroma - bagara egg masala being one such instance.
0000000085	Now you don't need to spend hours in the kitchen preparing meals, make this multi-purpose gravy once and it will help you make different curries.
0000000086	On the days you are pressed for time and are having a hard time managing everything, cooking even a 2-course meal feels like an impossible task.
0000000087	You may even find yourself wishing for some magic trick, but we've got no way out of days like these than to cook that dreaded meal.
0000000088	The chicken and rice are both cooked in the fresh flavours of coriander, mint and chillies.
0000000089	We learn how you eat your food is as important as the food you choose to eat.
0000000090	700 years after his death, this series explores the contemporary meaning of the seven cardinal sins.
0000000091	Just chop some of your vegetables, add this thick delicious gravy and you'll be all done in a matter of minutes.
0000000092	The versatility of this gravy will help you make almost any curry from chicken to aloo, mixed veg or matar paneer, you name it and we've got it covered.
0000000093	All you need to do is at the beginning of the week, prepare a large amount of this all-in-one-gravy and store it in an air-tight container in the fridge.
0000000094	And the best part is, egg curry leaves you with enough room to experiment.
0000000095	Slightly fry paneer chunks and keep them aside, in a pan heat some oil and add a cup of this gravy. 
0000000096	Add the paneer chunks, matar and adjust salt. A drizzle of some cream and your rich matar paneer is ready to be served.
0000000097	Marinate chicken with curd and some masala. Fry until golden brown and add in the all-in-one gravy.
0000000098	Just add some chicken masala in the end and coriander to garnish and your restaurant style chicken curry is ready to be served.
0000000099	Chop all the variety you got and slightly sauté them for a couple of minutes.
0000000100	Its taste is almost uniquely bitter, and yet its popularity boomed in the US during the 20th Century.
0000000101	Boil potatoes and cut them in cubes, slightly sauté them and keep them aside. In a pan heat oil and mix the gravy
0000000102	Add water according to your liking and drop the boiled potatoes to this. Mash a couple of potatoes for a perfect aloo ki sabji for your breakfast puri.
0000000103	For  Lauki kofta curry, Grate lauki and mix with besan and other dry masalas and make flat koftas out of this batter.
0000000104	Heat the gravy and dip the koftas in it, garnish with coriander and a simple yet delicious curry is ready for when the guests arrive.
0000000105	An Indian restaurant in England came up with a Grand Thali challenge of finishing a whopping 7kg Thali within an hour.
0000000106	All food lovers think that they have an enviable appetite, but very few people are actually blessed with the metabolism to consume copious amounts of food in one sitting.
0000000107	If you are one of these lucky folks, an Indian restaurant in England may just be the perfect place for you.
0000000108	The restaurant named Lily's Vegetarian Indian Cuisine is serving what it calls the "Grand Thali" and has spun a challenge around it.
0000000109	Served on a 24-inch platter with an assortment of 50 dishes weighing over 7kg, The idea is to finish the entire Thali within the time span of one hour.
0000000110	From a photo shared on Facebook, we were able to spot eight varieties of rotis, three types of rice, sixteen curries and sabji, three dips, six desserts, two lassis, and two savoury snacks.
0000000111	Aloo poha is a yummy and delicious breakfast dish that everybody in your family will love as it adds the favourite potato to a classic Indian breakfast.
0000000112	Thinking about what to make for breakfast gets confusing. We know only how to make a few recipes but we are bored of repeating them.
0000000113	The process of making keto medu vada is very similar to making normal medu vada. 
0000000114	Scientists have found evidence of ancient beer production from different kinds of crops all over the world.
0000000115	Keeping these things in my mind, I have found a breakfast recipe that we all know and love but has a simple twist to it.
0000000116	Aloo poha is a yummy and delicious breakfast that everybody in your family will enjoy as it adds the favourite potato to a classic Indian breakfast.
0000000117	The recipe for aloo poha is very similar to making kanda poha. The best part about this recipe is that it wouldn't take a lot of time to create something unique.
0000000118	To make this recipe, you need all the ingredients to make a poha along with boiled potatoes.
0000000119	Adding boiled potatoes to the poha reduces the cooking time, making this breakfast quick to make.
0000000120	 Cooking the potatoes with poha might burn the dish as potato takes time to cook and poha doesn't.
0000000121	Another important tip for making poha is the washing of raw poha. Washed poha becomes soggy after 5-10 minutes.
0000000122	It is essential to wash the poha for 5 minutes before putting it in the pan if you want fresh and flaky poha.
0000000123	As the diet grows in popularity, the demand for more Keto-friendly foods is also growing. Try this delicious Keto-friendly medu vada recipe at home.
0000000124	South Indian food is one of the healthiest cuisines in India. With its methods of cooking and unique ingredients, South Indian food is light on the stomach and yummy.
0000000125	South Indian food is one of the healthiest cuisine that is why you will see people eat idli chutney and sambhar dosa for all three meals, breakfast lunch and dinner.
0000000126	Medu vada might just be the least healthy dish within the cuisine that too because it is deep-fried. But that is not a problem for keto-diet.
0000000127	The only difference between the two is that the flour used to make the former is keto-friendly.
0000000128	On a normal healthy diet, urad dal would be considered a healthy ingredient but in a keto diet, one is not allowed to have pulses.
0000000129	This keto-recipe uses a combination of almond flour, coconut flour, psyllium husk and xanthan gum. These ingredients are keto-friendly to consume.
0000000130	Usually, deep-fried food is a big no in weight loss diets. In keto, high fat is encouraged and therefore deep-fried food is allowed to be eaten.
0000000131	To make this dish, start by adding all the flours to a bowl. To the dry flour, add all the spices. Pour water into the dry dough mixture as required.
0000000132	Make sure it results in a tight and wet dough. Divide the dough equally into small balls and shape the balls into doughnuts.
0000000133	Deep fry the raw doughnuts and your medu vada are ready. Serve it hot with coconut chutney.
0000000134	The Indian food diversity is so immense that if you start counting the number of food items you can have from a state, there will be no end to it.
0000000135	From classic dishes to street food and new fusion foods, there are thousands of things to try. 
0000000136	Farming may be among the last industries to undergo a digital revolution, but the changes are arguably going to be further reaching than anything we've seen so far.
0000000137	Mumbai is famous for its vada paos, pao bhaji, dabeli, misul, and so much more but the one thing which stands among these dishes is the lip-smacking Frankie.
0000000138	Filled with vegetables, sauces, masalas, and a Tikki- the humble Frankie is a delicious treat.
0000000139	While searching for some easy recipes and regional specialities, we came across this recipe of Mumbai style Tikki Frankie which is super easy to make.
0000000140	People of all ages will love this recipe. So, without waiting any further, let's jump into the recipe of this Frankie.
0000000141	First, heat some butter and add boiled potatoes, chopped onion, garlic, peas and masalas. Cook these for a while and then make tikkis out of them.
0000000142	Then in a separate bowl, add some wheat, maida and knead the dough. Roll out the dough and cook it well from both sides.
0000000143	Once done, add some yummy green chutney, put the tikkis, and add vegetables like capsicum and onion.
0000000144	He added that most of these people have never done rigorous exercises such as running, skipping, sports or jumping.
0000000145	To make the spring roll sheet, you would require one cup of all-purpose flour, some salt, mix water until a thin consistency is formed.
0000000146	Take a non-stick pan, spread some oil, drop one ladle of the batter, and spread it evenly Cook on low flame until it becomes transparent. Then remove and put aside.
0000000147	For the filling of the spring roll, you would need onion, chillies, poha, coriander, red chilli powder, garam masala, jeera powder, dhaniya powder, salt and lemon juice.
0000000148	He added that stress fractures are the most regular injury seen in athletes and military recruits.
0000000149	Indian cuisine consists of a variety of regional and traditional cuisines native to the Indian subcontinent.
0000000150	Sari is a single cloth ethnic wear for Indian women that is comfortable to use.
0000000151	Maybe it's the fiery masala and that thick iron griddle called tawa.
0000000152	Cows are considered sacred in India.
0000000153	India is the wettest inhabited place on Earth.
0000000154	India has over 300,000 mosques.
0000000155	India has over 2 million Hindu temples.
0000000156	Chenab Bridge is the highest rail bridge in the world.
0000000157	Rajasthan has a Temple of Rats.
0000000158	You can drive on the world’s highest motorable road.
0000000159	The popular game “Snakes and Ladders” originated in India.
0000000160	India was the first country to mine diamonds.
0000000161	Hinduism is the oldest religion in the world.
0000000162	India has 22 recognized languages.
0000000163	India Ranked the second-most populous country in the world.
0000000164	Most Indians eat with only their fingers.
0000000165	"Indian food" has become one of the most widespread cuisines in the world.
0000000166	India has the highest population of vegetarians.
0000000167	Holi is much more than a colorful powder festival.
0000000168	The world’s largest sundial is located in India.
0000000169	The Taj Mahal is slowly changing color.
0000000170	The Kumbh Mela is visible from space.
0000000171	India has one of the lowest divorce rates in the world.
0000000172	The Hindu calendar has six seasons.
0000000173	Varanasi is the most ancient surviving city in the world.
0000000174	Tea is the national beverage of India.
0000000175	Around 70% of the world’s spices come from India.
0000000176	India has the current tallest statue in the world.
0000000177	The Amritsar Golden Temple serves free meals.
0000000178	India was the first country to refine and consume sugar.
0000000179	Shampos are originated in India.
0000000180	India is Famous for its Iconic Step Wells.
0000000181	Gandhi is one of India’s most famous icons.
0000000182	There’s a floating post office in India.
0000000183	Half of the population in India is under 25 years old.
0000000184	The most popular sport in India is cricket.
0000000185	Indians love to eat vegetables. 
0000000186	India has 51 births per minute.
0000000187	India is part of Asia.
0000000188	India is an English speaking country.
0000000189	India is the world’s second-largest English speaking country. 
0000000190	India has a population of more than 1.3 billion
0000000191	India's population is growing dramatically.
0000000192	India is expected to be the world’s most populated country.
0000000193	There are 29 states in India.
0000000194	Delhi is the most populated city in India.
0000000195	India has many different cultures.
0000000196	Festivals and holidays are almost endless in India.
0000000197	The name 'India' originated from a river.
0000000198	"India" was acquired from the River Sindhu also known as Indus River.
0000000199	The official currency is known as Rupee.
0000000200	The official currency of India is called Rupee.
0000000201	India has 6 seasons in the Hindu calendar.
0000000202	Namaste' is an Indian greeting.
0000000203	Families in India stay together under one roof.
0000000204	One big happy family is common in India wherein parents.
0000000205	Cow is regarded as the Holy Animal in India.
0000000206	Fasting is a basic part of Hindu culture.
0000000207	Fire plays an important part in an Indian wedding.
0000000208	Indian couple exchanges their vows around the Agni.
0000000209	India has all religions in the world.
0000000210	India has the most number of mosques in the world.
0000000211	Different regions in India have their own signature dishes.
0000000212	Indian food is an essential part of their culture.
0000000213	Chai is more than just a cup of tea.
0000000214	 India is also the 2nd largest producer of tea in the whole world.
0000000215	Bollywood is the Hollywood of India.
0000000216	Bollywood is the largest film producer in India.
0000000217	Bollywood is also one of the largest film producers in the world.
0000000218	There are 8 types of classical dance in India.
0000000219	The Kumbh Mela festival in India is a major pilgrimage in Hinduism.
0000000220	The Kumbh Mela is celebrated 4 times over 12 years.
0000000221	Each time, over a hundred million people attend the Kumbh Mela Festival.
0000000222	Kumbh Mela Festival is the world’s biggest gathering of humans. 
0000000223	Police officers are given higher pay for having a mustache.
0000000224	Women in India own 11% of the world's gold.
0000000225	India is the world’s oldest, largest and continuous civilization.
0000000226	India is also one of the largest democracies in the world.
0000000227	India has the largest postal system in the world.
0000000228	India has the world’s only floating post office on Dal Lake, Sri Nagar.
0000000229	Using just your hands to eat a range of food takes skill and practice. 
0000000230	The second largest pool of engineers and scientists is from India.
0000000231	India is the only country to have an entire ocean named after it.
0000000232	India has the fastest growing telecom market in the world.
0000000233	India has the cheapest telecom tariff in the world.
0000000234	Navi Mumbai is the largest planned city in the world.
0000000235	London has more Indian restaurants than Mumbai or Delhi.
0000000236	Fauja Singh is the oldest marathon runner in the world.
0000000237	Bollywood is the largest movie industry in terms of output.
0000000238	India’s space program is among the top five space programs in the world.
0000000239	India is the 7th largest country in the world.
0000000240	The City Montessori School is the world’s largest school in terms of students.
0000000241	India is the world’s largest milk producer.
0000000242	Over 4700 daily newspapers are produced in India.
0000000243	KFC provides a vegetarian menu in India.
0000000244	The largest wholesale spice market of Asia is in India.
0000000245	India’s road network is the world’s second largest.
0000000246	India is house to the world’s biggest family.
0000000247	"Zero" in the number system was invented by a mathematician from India.
0000000248	Chess was invented in India.
0000000249	Yoga originated from India and is still in existence for over 5000 years.
0000000250	Calculus, Trigonometry, and Algebra originated in India.
0000000251	Takshila, the first-ever university in the world started around 700 BC in India.
0000000252	India is the place of origin of Buddhism and Jainism.
0000000253	India has the world’s highest cricket ground which is in Chail, Himachal Pradesh.
0000000254	More than 54 crore people voted in 2014 general elections.
0000000255	Indian railway employs more than a million people.
0000000256	Indian railway is the largest employers in the world.
0000000257	Indian Railways has world’s 4th longest rail network.
0000000258	There is a lake built in India due to the impact of a meteor.
0000000259	Vande Mataram is India’s national song.
0000000260	Jana Gana Mana is India’s national anthem.
0000000261	Indian Lotus is its national flower.
0000000262	Indira Gandhi was India’s first and the only female Prime Minister till date.
0000000263	White tigers are only found among Indian tigers.
0000000264	Mango is India’s national fruit.
0000000265	Peacock is India’s national bird.
0000000266	The first mining of diamonds was done in India.
0000000267	 India was the first to detect water on the Moon.
0000000268	The Taj Mahal is one of the Seven Wonders of the World.
0000000269	There is only one time zone across all of India.
0000000270	It is illegal to carry Indian currency, Rupee, outside of India.
0000000271	Pooja rooms stand as a place of peace in one's home.
0000000272	Indian weddings are a colourful occasion.
0000000273	In India, there isn’t one national language.
0000000274	The sari dates back to at least 3000 BCE.
0000000275	Sari wearers often choose the colour of their garment based on the occasion.
0000000276	Red sari is often worn by brides to symbolise fertility and prosperity.
0000000277	Indiai is one of the fastest growing major economies in the world.
0000000278	Discover the craft behind the harvesting of these luxurious shelled creatures.
0000000279	In terms of purchasing power India is the world's third-largest economy.
0000000280	Roughly 67 percent of the world’s outsourcing is done in India.
0000000281	The Indian IT industry is valued at US 150- billion.
0000000282	In rural Bihar, Nalanda, one of the world's most ancient universities is being rebuilt.
0000000283	India's cuisine made of local spices, herbs, vegetables and fruits.
0000000284	Indian cuisine may be the oldest continuously prepared cuisine in known human history. 
0000000285	Alcohol consumption is banned in five Indian states.
0000000286	Chicken tikka masala has become one of Britain’s national dish.
0000000287	Khari Baoli in Delhi is Asia's largest wholesale spice market.
0000000288	India is home to the wettest inhabited place on earth.
0000000289	A boy named John was upset.
0000000290	His father found him crying.
0000000291	Chop onions and cut tomatoes into small cubes.
0000000292	Add ginger garlic and sauté until raw smell is gone.
0000000293	Add onions and all the dry masala and cook until mixed together.
0000000294	Add tomatoes and let cook until soft and mushy.
0000000295	In the end add salt and kasuri methi if you are using it.
0000000296	Cook this masala until everything has been mixed properly.
0000000297	Cook this masala until it starts leaving oil in the sides.
0000000298	Take off the heat; let it cool properly before pouring them in airtight containers.
0000000299	Now that you've prepared the gravy.
0000000300	How To Make An All-In-One Gravy.