Female_Emma
I understand. It sounds like a place that is both impressive and terrifying. I wonder what kind of tea they serve there. Is it made from the sun's rays or from something else? And who are the people who live there? Are they loyal to the Empire or do they have their own agendas?

Male_Andrew
Yes, that is what I said. A maximin strategy is the one that maximizes the minimum payoff of a player, regardless of what the other players do. It is a way of ensuring that the player gets at least a certain amount of payoff, even in the worst case scenario.

Male_Brian
If you can't find the information, you may want to consider contacting your state's insurance department. They may be able to help you locate any life insurance policies that were taken out on your husband. I hope this helps. Please let me know if you have any other questions.
