0000000001	This time last year, the pastry chef duo sat in their Chicago apartment wondering what to do next.
0000000002	The pandemic had shut down restaurants. They had lost their paychecks. They had to make a decision.
0000000003	This was after the two of us had the highest-paying, most comfortable jobs in our career history.
0000000004	This dish has graced the Felidia menu since the very beginning. It’s simple and fresh, and an absolute guest favorite.
0000000005	Moving is nothing new for Nugent and Ramos, Hogsalt's former executive pastry and bakery director. 
0000000006	Have your fishmonger select fish that are all about the same size, so they cook at the same rate.
0000000007	Six years ago, Melisa and David Root planted themselves in Portland, Oregon, hoping to start a small restaurant empire.
0000000008	They say you if you can make it past year five, you're going to start actually making some money.
0000000009	We had just started our fifth year; things were going really well for us... and then Covid hit.
0000000010	You cannot argue with the balance sheet and the books because they tell you the reality. But it still breaks my heart.
0000000011	With no real plan forward, they headed for the Rocky Mountains and Breckenridge, Colorado, where David was offered an executive chef position at Breckenridge Distillery's restaurant.
0000000012	This spring, a new opportunity presented itself to Melisa 1,700 miles away in the Blue Ridge Mountains. 
0000000013	She relocated closer to sea level in Charlottesville, Virginia, to start a new pastry program at the Farmington Country Club.
0000000014	For now, the couple will live two time zones apart, with the hope of someday living in the same place again.
0000000015	Renowned for its nourishing simplicity, Greek cuisine is considered among the finest and healthiest in the world. 
0000000016	With an emphasis on baked rather than fried food, most traditional dishes avoid elaborate sauces, preferring the perfume of herb seasonings.
0000000017	Indeed, one Greek island, Ikaria, has been under the microscope in recent years, as one in three of its 8,500-odd residents are over 90 years old. 
0000000018	While there may be other lifestyle components involved, a typical Greek diet appears to be a major factor here.
0000000019	The worst tongue twister on a list of starters, this pungent dip consists of a starchy base of soaked breadcrumbs or potatoes with added lemon juice and olive oil.
0000000020	While dried haricot bean soup fed hungry Greeks during the German occupation in World War II, the dish is now somewhat looked down on.
0000000021	Surprisingly though, its sister dish, a hearty plate of giant baked beans seasoned with cilantro, has made it to the typical mezze spread. 
0000000022	For the berry sauce, in a medium saucepan, combine 2 cups blueberries, 2 cups strawberries, the granulated sugar, orange zest and juice, jam, and rum.
0000000023	Bring to a simmer, and cook to make a slightly syrupy sauce, about 10 to 15 minutes. 
0000000024	This nutritious soup is renowned for its curative properties and looks deceptively easy to make.
0000000025	The cooking process actually involves slowly boiling a whole chicken in a pot with vegetables and bonnet rice and then picking the meat off, discarding the skin and bones.
0000000026	At this point, you break a couple of yolks into a bowl and slowly pour some of the broth while whisking.
0000000027	Squeeze in some lemon juice and stir the bowl's liquid carefully back into the pot -- it won't curdle if just simmering.
0000000028	The result is a rich, silky smooth soup that marries fat, carbs and protein with vitamin C.
0000000029	Put the remaining 2 cups blueberries, remaining 4 cups strawberries, and the superfine sugar in a medium bowl. Toss to combine, and let sit at room temperature 10 minutes.
0000000030	In a mixer fitted with the paddle attachment, mix the ricotta and mascarpone at medium  speed  for a few seconds to combine, then add the superfine sugar and vanilla.
0000000031	To assemble, soak half of the Savoiardi in the cooked berry sauce until moistened, rolling them around to coat thoroughly.
0000000032	By far the best known Greek dish internationally, typifying the country's cuisine, moussaka is also one of the most elaborate.
0000000033	Here minced meat, slices of potatoes and eggplant are separately fried before being layered in a baking pan and topped with a béchamel sauce. 
0000000034	Spoon a few spoonfuls of the remaining cooked berry sauce over the Savoiardi. Spread half of the ricotta mixture in an even layer over the Savoiardi.
0000000035	This is because of the lack of space for raising large animals in the confines of a walled town or castle.
0000000036	Brought to Greece by the Venetians, it's an unusually calorific course in a country of light meals.
0000000037	Orzo is cooked together with meat in oven dishes, while spaghetti is almost exclusively eaten as a bolognese, flavor-enhanced by cinnamon and all spice.
0000000038	It may look like moussaka, but the air trapped along the macaroni renders it a fluffier, lighter meal.
0000000039	Soak the remaining Savoiardi in the cooked berry sauce, and arrange in a tight layer over the fresh berries. Spread the remaining mascarpone over this in a smooth layer.
0000000040	You can pick up these rings of baked bread dough covered in sesame seeds from street vendor stands in every Greek city. 
0000000041	Combine the remaining fresh berries and any cooked berry sauce left from soaking the Savoiardi, cover, and chill overnight.
0000000042	To serve, cut squares of the tiramisù and serve with a little of the leftover berries and sauce.
0000000043	Other countries take a similar "more is more" approach to Easter meals, but a few dishes really stand out. Here are just five.
0000000044	Mix together cocoa powder and cinnamon in a small bowl and sift overtop using a fine mesh strainer.
0000000045	Finish by grating or making curls of white chocolate to sprinkle over top. Then dip cranberries in corn syrup.
0000000046	To make the pie, first, you need to make the pastry dough, which includes flour, eggs, salt, milk and lard.
0000000047	She learned about it from other Italian Americans while she was working at a clothing factory in Brooklyn, New York. 
0000000048	She took their version and made some additions and subtractions. After years and years of tweaks, she created her own Italian American tradition.
0000000049	Her secret is extra-sharp provolone. Rago said it's one of the most popular dishes on her website, and everyone who tries it says they have success their first try.
0000000050	When you think of authentic Mexican cuisine, there are many things that come to mind: rice, beans and tortillas, to name a few.
0000000051	Capirotada is a Mexican dessert that's similar to bread pudding. It's made from bread drenched in syrup and layered among nuts, cheese, fruit and sometimes sprinkles.
0000000052	Martinez was born and raised in Tampico, Mexico. She serves this dish for dessert every Easter.
0000000053	The bread is placed in a ovenproof dish between layers of cotija cheese, roasted peanuts and raisins. It's baked and then topped with bananas and sprinkles.
0000000054	Capirotada is usually served at room temperature on Easter Sunday, but many serve it throughout Holy Week.
0000000055	Get it and I could maybe melt in more with the white majority — a weird mystique to latch onto a box of tiny luncheon meat and crackers, I know.
0000000056	Brought to Mexico by the Spaniards, capirotada became popular in Mexico because it's easy to make and uses ingredients people have on hand.
0000000057	It was originally a savory dish using beef broth, but evolved into today's sweet version using syrup, according to Martinez.
0000000058	Shake off any excess syrup and then dip in white sugar. Garnish any way you desire with cranberries and mint.
0000000059	Scoop ice cream into heat proof low glasses, place in freezer on a tray until ready to serve. 
0000000060	This soup is often served with a boiled egg and sausage, and then garnished with spicy horseradish.
0000000061	Mix flour and cold water with aromatics (including garlic, allspice, peppercorns, marjoram and bay leaves). Then, let it sit on your counter for several days to ferment. 
0000000062	It is certainly a favourite in our restaurants, but it is easy to make at home as well.
0000000063	This soup is served all over the country year-round and on Easter with many variations. Some have it with sauerkraut and smoked goat cheese. 
0000000064	Pinpointing dishes authentic to Singapore might seem like an impossible feat, but that's exactly the endeavor chef Damian D'Silva has chosen.
0000000065	Little did he know that the resulting game would go on to become one of the greatest, most addictive and most successful of all time.
0000000066	That includes one in six children — a number that spikes in the north, reaching 60 per cent in Nunavut — and which creates greater risk for depression and suicide.
0000000067	The beverages are low in sugar, have no artificial flavours or preservatives and feature ingredients such as turmeric and goji berry powder, which are both touted for their health benefits.
0000000068	To simplify things, he knocked that down to four squares, thus reducing the number of shapes from 12 to seven. 
0000000069	He called the game Tetris, combining the Greek numeral "tetra" (meaning four) and tennis, his favorite sport.
0000000070	It was only through the sheer brilliance of its design that Tetris was transformed from a quirky test program into a worldwide phenomenon.
0000000071	Ideas were owned by the state and the very concept of selling software as a product was unfamiliar to him. 
0000000072	People were just sharing Tetris through word of mouth and by copying it onto floppy disks.
0000000073	Then, Pajitnov heard rumors that the game might have crossed borders and was being played in other Eastern bloc countries.
0000000074	Stein, however, interpreted his response as a green light and immediately started producing the game. 
0000000075	Meanwhile, in a small bowl, toss the breadcrumbs with 2 teaspoons of the garlic oil and the chopped thyme.
0000000076	It said that the rights had not been officially granted and that his launch was illegal.
0000000077	As a mom to children with celiac disease and peanut allergies, Miriam Pearl knows all too well the challenges of creating fun, flavourful and safe dishes for her loved ones.
0000000078	Rogers set out to obtain the necessary permissions, and soon realized what a challenge that would be.
0000000079	Maybe you have a natural affinity for making and managing money. Or maybe you're just trying not to make a hash of it.
0000000080	Either way, someone at some point in your life likely dropped a pearl of wisdom in your lap that has made your financial life better than it would have been otherwise.
0000000081	He was in his early 30s and working as an engineering manager at a local television station in Hartford, Connecticut. 
0000000082	Roast the fish and vegetables until the fish are cooked through and the vegetables are just tender, about 20 minutes, tossing the vegetables once or twice.
0000000083	Vigneaux has since given the same advice to friends and family. And today, mostly retired, he says he and his wife aren't rich but live comfortably without financial stress.
0000000084	Getting the managers to try the food simply served as a reminder that what is currently on the menu is bland and not something most people would choose to eat.
0000000085	Today at 46, Schmidt said he and his wife are debt free, having paid off their mortgage in 16 years.
0000000086	If you want to cook with them right away give it a gentle squeeze; if it's too firm, put it down and pick up a peach that's a little softer.
0000000087	Nearing retirement from a 23-year career in the military, he decided to invest a small amount of money with a broker.
0000000088	After retiring from the service in 2015 Blount became a federal contractor. He's 65 today and plans to work until he's 70.
0000000089	In this recipe I used a hand blender or immersion blender, but a regular blender or hand whisk will produce the same results (however, the hand whisk might take longer).
0000000090	Instead of gorging on a big bag of chips or a box of Timbits, keep your diet in check by packing healthy snacks to take on the road with you.
0000000091	He knows he's lucky to have entered the stock market when it was "going sideways" coming out of the Great Recession.
0000000092	Trying to stick to a diet that is so rigid you can never eat what you really love is a waste of time because you're going to blow it.
0000000093	Three years ago, when she was 22, Sarah Williams had her first job out of college. But she made so little that she bartended at night for extra cash. 
0000000094	Even then, she couldn't make ends meet between her living expenses, credit card debt and student loan debt.
0000000095	She used to tell me, 'Budget realistically and make sure to include the things you like to do for fun or to treat yourself. 
0000000096	She also set up a schedule to work down her debt, starting with the smallest credit card balances first. 
0000000097	And throughout the pandemic she continued making her student loan payments even though she was allowed to defer them.
0000000098	Gary Anderson credits his dad with teaching him the importance of saving for retirement early on.
0000000099	He then encouraged his future wife to do the same. Now in their early 50s and hoping to retire sooner rather than later, they're glad they did, Anderson said.
0000000100	Never have more than one mortgage and car payment at a time and carry no other debt.
0000000101	Before you get married, make an agreement with your spouse-to-be that you will never spend money behind each other's backs.
0000000102	Spending behind your spouse's back is to defy the marriage contract and will land you in divorce court.
0000000103	But to him, the most important financial wisdom they ever imparted had less to do with how to make money than it did with how to use it well.
0000000104	Sure, that’s why many of us have credit cards — for emergencies, but when you’re paying off a bill that can easily add up to thousands, save where you can.
0000000105	As a parent, you can use this gift of extra time to connect more deeply with your child and teach them the joy of being with and caring for others.
0000000106	In fact, a recent study by the USDA suggests that refined sugars are so harmful to the development of children, they should be completely avoided before the age of two.
0000000107	If the floors of your unit are in good shape there’s really no need for your landlord or property manager to change it, whether you like the style or not.
0000000108	If your home will be unoccupied while you’re away, consider adding motion sensor lights, which Redfin reports are a great DIY project that will keep your house safe and secure.
0000000109	With realistic and balanced expectations, parents can learn to reap the benefits of a remote world while encouraging children to live a life of greater awareness, gratitude, kindness and purpose.
0000000110	The reward doesn’t need to be in the form of food (and it actually shouldn’t), rather extra minutes for playtime outside before bed, or a tangible object like a sticker.
0000000111	Book a hotel in close proximity to a drug or department store so that you’ll always have access to diapers, wipes, snacks, and other items that you may have forgotten.
0000000112	Make arrangements for friends and relatives to serve a different range of tasks such as being pallbearers, helping arrange the funeral service to lending a hand in purchasing funeral flowers.
0000000113	Now, I believe that a good educator won’t just tell a child how to do a task, they will allow them to experiment and struggle with it for a while.
0000000114	His in-laws would pay for far-flung relatives to travel to family gatherings. And most impressive was how well they supported their own aging parents.
0000000115	A fillet of fish is convenient and easy to cook and eat, but there is nothing better than a whole roasted fish for flavor.
0000000116	The median price for an existing home in June hit an all-time high of $363,300, up 23% over last year. That marks 112 straight months of year-over-year gains.
0000000117	Supply has modestly improved in recent months due to more housing starts and existing homeowners listing their homes, all of which has resulted in an uptick in sales.
0000000118	Home sales continue to run at a pace above the rate seen before the pandemic.
0000000119	At the end of June there were 1.25 million homes for sale, up 3.3% from May's inventory and down 18.8% from one year ago.
0000000120	Once the mail starts coming to your house, you can now easily identify any subscriptions and accounts you have to go and request to be closed due to the user’s passing.
0000000121	At the current sales pace, that equates to a 2.6-month supply. A balanced market between homebuyers and sellers generally needs a 6-month supply.
0000000122	Ideally, the costs for a home would rise roughly in line with income growth, which is likely to happen in 2022 as more listings and new construction become available.
0000000123	While the median price of a home continues to go up, some of that price growth is because more larger, expensive homes are selling.
0000000124	An animal law non-profit group is calling on the Ontario government to investigate Marineland's treatment of Kiska the orca.
0000000125	It alleges Marineland is breaking the law by subjecting the orca to conditions that don't meet her physical and mental needs.
0000000126	Animal Justice's complaint follows videos posted by Phil Demers, a whistleblower who is also a former trainer at the Niagara Falls aquarium.
0000000127	Animal Justice states Kiska was captured in Iceland in 1979 when she was three years old before Marineland purchased her. 
0000000128	The group says Kiska gave birth to five calves, but they all died young. Over time, it says, her other companions died or moved to other facilities.
0000000129	While it's illegal to keep whales and dolphins in captivity, Marineland has an exemption because of the rule's grandfather clause.
0000000130	Animal Justice highlighted the Provincial Animal Welfare Services Act, which states an animal's owner cannot cause or permit distress.
0000000131	While we wholeheartedly believe that salads are a year-round food we get why the warmer months really bring on 'salad season'. 
0000000132	All that fresh in-season produce to eat raw, plus many of them are quick, light and ideal for when the heat waves hit. 
0000000133	Here are 36 salads to enjoy this season: vivid and crisp, leafy, loaded with legumes and grains, grilled to perfection, and some full of fruit too.
0000000134	For an intricate plated design, use all three flavours of gelatin and three moulds that vary in size and shape.
0000000135	In this case, you will have extra prepared gelatin, simply add to a separate bowl, refrigerate and let set and reserve for another use.
0000000136	For the cherry gelatin mould, lightly spray four larger-sized moulds with cooking spray — you can use mini bundt cake pans or other food-safe moulds.
0000000137	For the lemon gelatin mould, lightly spray four medium-sized moulds with cooking spray. You can use mini tart shell pans or other food-safe moulds.
0000000138	Pour mixture into prepared medium moulds. Refrigerate for 3 to 4 hours or until completely set. 
0000000139	For the orange gelatin mould, lightly spray four small-sized moulds with cooking spray. You can use small round chocolate moulds or other food-safe moulds.
0000000140	Empty package of orange gelatin powder into a bowl; set aside. Combine ½ cup water and ½ can evaporated milk in a small saucepan; bring to a boil. 
0000000141	Pour boiling mixture over orange gelatin powder. Stir constantly until orange powder is completely dissolved, about 2 to 3 minutes.
0000000142	Pour in remaining ½ can of evaporated milk; stir until blended. Pour mixture into prepared moulds. Refrigerate for 3 to 4 hours or until completely set. 
0000000143	In a large bowl, beat marshmallow fluff until it loosens slightly. In batches, add in whipped topping and whip until smooth and creamy. 
0000000144	Fold in shredded coconut and coconut extract (if using) until well blended. Use right away or store in a covered container for 2 to 3 hours. 
0000000145	Spoon or smear Whipped Coconut Marshmallow Cream onto four plates. Unmold gelatin moulds and arrange on each plate. Garnish with fruit and coconut flakes.
0000000146	It’s so easy to fall back on classics like Chicken Caesars or taco bowls, but variety truly is the spice of life. 
0000000147	Mix things up and toss any of your favourite greens with juicy watermelon, crunchy fennel and a simple homemade citrus vinaigrette.
0000000148	Combine basil, orange zest, orange juice, vinegar, honey, garlic, mustard, salt and pepper in a blender. Pulse until very finely chopped. 
0000000149	With the motor running on low, slowly drizzle in the oil until smooth and emulsified. Transfer to an air-tight container and store in the refrigerator for up to 3 days.
0000000150	Toss greens with fennel, watermelon, radishes, olives and red onion. Drizzle with half the dressing; toss lightly to coat. Divide among dinner plates or arrange on a large, shallow platter.
0000000151	That is why we feel cheated by hollow walls, flimsy doors, and shaky balustrades.
0000000152	Virtually every city administration would undertake at least one campaign to clean up Times Square.
0000000153	She has been married and divorced twice.
0000000154	To the north, mountains blanketed with palms rise alongside the shoreline.
0000000155	This simultaneous Home Movies posting is at an end.
0000000156	Combine the onion halves and tomatoes in a large bowl.
0000000157	Arrange the vegetables on another baking sheet, setting the tomatoes cut side up. 
0000000158	Mr. inaudible says it takes ten years to learn the full repertoire of Burundi dance.
0000000159	Big turnovers by Stewart, who threw three interceptions, helped Denver.
0000000160	I'm telling you, the charming, graceful sick person is just a myth, an urban legend.
0000000161	This was matched by a dive downward by bassoons, bass clarinet, trombones and bass tuba.
0000000162	As evening approaches, tennis, volleyball, and softball get going.
0000000163	The Tokyo Olympics is hit by a spate of coronavirus cases.
0000000164	While annoying, slamming seems to happen to very few consumers.
0000000165	The winery's diaphanous stone facade links it to the architects' European work.
0000000166	We have techniques for grilling corn.
0000000167	This is, however, accompanied by a lack of fast twitch fibers.
0000000168	I kind of dug the stabs made at evolving Nikita's character under extreme circumstances.
0000000169	Remove the fish from the oven, and tent with foil to keep warm. 
0000000170	After the crash, their relationship became known.
0000000171	They removed the CD drives.
0000000172	Gatorade has Alpine Snow, Riptide Rush, and Glacier Freeze.
0000000173	Every Coen opus after Blood Simple has, in one way or another, fallen flat.
0000000174	No, correction, they're not losing, they're getting spanked.
0000000175	In the trio, Emily Coates and Isabel Kimmel, in debuts, sparkled alongside Arch Higgins.
0000000176	Scatter the breadcrumbs over the vegetables, and increase oven temperature to 450 degrees.
0000000177	We had compulsory attendance at Episcopal chapel services eight times a week.
0000000178	The lawsuits, if successful, could significantly help Netscape over the long run, company officials acknowledge.
0000000179	They say American policy will change only when Cuba's politics do.
0000000180	Lieutenant, thanks very much for joining us.
0000000181	Competing cities hungry for an NFL franchise drive up the ante with taxpayer dollars.
0000000182	I'm Theresa Erickson, along with Tony Riggs bringing you VOA News Now from Washington.
0000000183	Granules not eaten by slugs biodegrade after two weeks and provide beneficial soil nutrients.
0000000184	Seasoning is salt, pepper and perhaps cayenne.
0000000185	Readership declines through the week and is lowest on the weekends.
0000000186	Fredric Flom was just shy of his third birthday when Cunningham was writing.
0000000187	San Francisco is hosting Houston.
0000000188	Then there's Malkovich, who does a Russian mafioso the way Olivier would have done one.
0000000189	You'd be surprised at just how outrageous or outlandish some of the claims are.
0000000190	Irrigation flows uninterrupted to alfalfa, citrus, cotton and vegetable crops in Yuma County and elsewhere.
0000000191	Large, multinational issues such as American Express, General Motors and Eastman Kodak led the declines.
0000000192	Articles dealing with kidney and diuretics and dopamine were searched.
0000000193	Shopping arcades are a staple feature of every Japanese city, town, and village.
0000000194	By the late eighties, it was healthier food, with less fat and cholesterol.
0000000195	Crowds rampage through the streets, setting fires, breaking windows, and looting shops.
0000000196	Last night I wanted donuts.
0000000197	There are beautiful vistas, secluded villages, and a range of exhilarating walks en route.
0000000198	There was no claim of responsibility for Thursday's bombings, but police blame Muslim extremist rebels.
0000000199	They unsuccessfully tried to stonewall the move.
0000000200	Roast until crumbs are crisp, about 5 minutes. 
0000000201	Leaders claim Creech violated policy by going against united Methodist church rules.
0000000202	One audience member asks Seinfeld to list some of his favorite episodes.
0000000203	All aboard the platform have been evacuated.
0000000204	Core and very thinly slice two of the fennel bulbs.
0000000205	Scalia wrote the majority opinion, joined by Rehnquist, O'Connor, Kennedy and Thomas.
0000000206	They helped finish off his birthday cake while his other family enjoyed a cake, too.
0000000207	Our listener hotline is six one seven eight six eight five seven five zero.
0000000208	Their goal, however, appears more basic, some semblance of equal representation.
0000000209	Pathological findings in spontaneous rupture of the spleen include gross and microscopic changes.
0000000210	I really like her and, as you know, the whole psychiatric framing device.
0000000211	The Buffy Spinoff is dead, for multitudinous reasons.
0000000212	Each frame requires up to fifty megabytes of storage, meaning high computer costs.
0000000213	Keep them in ice water while you prepare the rest of the salad.
0000000214	Evander Holyfield knew if he lost, it was over.
0000000215	Second, unlike strict hierarchies, a child term may have more than one parent terms.
0000000216	Attack your accuser, any accuser, try to discredit them and destroy them.
0000000217	He has no campaign headquarters, no campaign manager, no campaign spokesman.
0000000218	A good movie with Godzilla in it may be by definition a bad Godzilla movie.
0000000219	But if the back door is closed, defended, keep passing.
0000000220	Without Rivera's protection, Trotsky was easier prey for Stalin's assassins.
0000000221	Stir the lemon juice and parsley into the remaining garlic oil.
0000000222	In our view, clarifying these issues is of considerable importance.
0000000223	Advertisers frequently urge us to rebel, and they frequently urge us to conform.
0000000224	Louise Woodward got a not-so-welcome home from the tabloids.
0000000225	These genes map to sites already known to be genetically altered in GCT specimens.
0000000226	Sam Donaldson, ABC News, with the President in Johannesburg, South Africa.
0000000227	Gaze out to sea, picnic on benches and watch fishermen hook herring.
0000000228	To generate the data, ships bounce sound signals off underground formations.
0000000229	He's a gastroenterologist, and she's a chef.
0000000230	We're thinking TiVo, here, if DH gets reimbursed for his iPad.
0000000231	The merger partners NationsBank and Bank of America, promising to give something back to their communities.
0000000232	In Taiwan, men are reportedly willing to pay twice that, sixty dollars a pill.
0000000233	Beginning in the late preschool years, children can learn to program.
0000000234	Still, Schuck noted, tobacco companies also know that their luck may not always hold.
0000000235	Backstage after a lecture to the Caltech faculty, Hawking is exhausted.
0000000236	Donald Rumsfeld creeps me out because he reminds me of the Mayor.
0000000237	I love Dole endorsing Bush at the same time Kennedy endorses Gore.
0000000238	Begin by making the crispy bits. 
0000000239	But Duke, hated Duke, has remained at large.
0000000240	Remove the foil from the fish, and serve with the vegetables.
0000000241	HIV has a long history of laughing last.
0000000242	Just beyond is Playa Miramar, prized by bodysurfers and boogie borders for its challenging waves.
0000000243	Or, possibly, just ask me nicely for a Thompson sampler.
0000000244	Drizzle the remaining oil over all.
0000000245	Both Chris Dudley and Buck Williams have missed playing time because of injuries.
0000000246	I'm starving, even though I've eaten dinner.
0000000247	Cells showing immunofluorescence for both MIF and TH were also observed.
0000000248	Its biggest imports are unassembled auto parts, computers and machinery.
0000000249	Lymphoid tissue sampling was first used as a preclinical test in sheep scrapie.
0000000250	I am moved to offer some armchair psychological analysis.
0000000251	Between Lori, Kat and Burrell, they broke me of my shopping phobia.
0000000252	Keep your eyes open for Renaissance details, grand doorways, and views into lovely courtyards.
0000000253	So we dragged all around downtown LA, the diamond district around Sixth and Spring.
0000000254	I was watching the rerun of Bill Maher's new show Real Time on HBO.
0000000255	You turned evil way sooner than we thought.
0000000256	Bradford Burns, a spokesman for WorldCom, declined to comment.
0000000257	The win in Toulouse kept Paraguay one point ahead of Spain, good enough to advance.
0000000258	Nuevo Vallarta is also the place to kayak a lagoon or swim with dolphins.
0000000259	The philharmonic orchestra in Boise, Idaho, will serenade late filers.
0000000260	Next, travelling counterclockwise, we reach the Dodecanese islands in the southeastern Aegean.
0000000261	Those missteps on the eighteenth hole may end up costing McGill and Inkster.
0000000262	In a sense, Russia has had a preview of a Chernomyrdin government.
0000000263	Maybe Father will respect me if I show off my translating skills.
0000000264	We apologize to our audience, Philip Morris and Reynolds.
0000000265	Second place was New Jersey, followed by Illinois, New Hampshire, Nevada, and Michigan.
0000000266	The building collapsed into itself, causing a ferocious windstorm and creating a massive debris cloud.
0000000267	Domestic violence survivors in Jackson, Vicksburg, Hattiesburg, Oxford and Pascagoula can all get help.
0000000268	Pool, grass, and hedge form a rectangle in a rectangle in a rectangle.
0000000269	But while Nicklaus and Watson shared a rivalry, they also shared a friendship.
0000000270	I woke up early with no Ambien hangover feeling and no rebound headache.
0000000271	Andre, no one in Hollywood is excited about growing old.
0000000272	In February, Danielle van Dam, seven, was abducted from her bedroom in San Diego.
0000000273	VOA White House Correspondent Deborah Tate reports on his stop in Champaign-Urbana, Illinois.
0000000274	Agatha says she and her neighbors rejoiced having survived the terrible ordeal unharmed.
0000000275	Exhibits cover fishing, seaborne trade, sea transport, and there is an aquarium.
0000000276	I'm Susan Yaki along with Tom Crosby.
0000000277	Mallorca and Menorca are justly famous for their leather industries.
0000000278	Defending champ Tiger Woods is one of eight golfers within two strokes.
0000000279	They have slashed welfare rolls and unemployment.
0000000280	The world isn't an agricultural society anymore.
0000000281	Separate budgets move daily with spot news, features, sports and commentary.
0000000282	We've resisted attempts to force us out, to marginalize us, to silence and intimidate us.
0000000283	I assumed he was going to kill it anyway.
0000000284	Kipple is the theory that if you leave trash unattended, it will multiply.
0000000285	Felix sat at his shoulder, hands folded in his lap, lips sealed.
0000000286	Or, to be more specific, in its region of origin.
0000000287	Newsweek says tourists and celebs are flocking to Patagonia, once a haven for escaped Nazis.
0000000288	White archly sought to differentiate between parent Enron and Enron Energy Services.
0000000289	Our guys are kind of half defensive lineman, half linebacker.
0000000290	Appell and his partner, Greg Mueller, disagree.
0000000291	There's new territory, there's new places to go, new things to explore.
0000000292	Reasonably priced salads, crepes, fresh fish and a large selection of ice cream are served.
0000000293	So the league took NBC's offer, added a bit, and ABC agreed.
0000000294	As far as I understood it, Windows didn't run on my Mac.
0000000295	Antacid tabs could take over forty five minutes to have an effect.
0000000296	Flowers, photographs and candles on a public thoroughfare do nothing meaningful to memorialize the deceased.
0000000297	Try pasting it into a new browser window, Robert.
0000000298	Put the potatoes in a large saucepan with salted water to cover. 
0000000299	Wrap the tails of the fish in foil to keep them from burning.
0000000300	Season the fish inside and out with salt and pepper.
0100000001	Did you not hear what I said?
0100000002	Am I allowed to say something?
0100000003	Is this the last of them?
0100000004	Can you pass me the salt?
0100000005	Is there nothing I can say to change your mind?
0100000006	Do you know what I mean?
0100000007	When does the meeting start?
0100000008	Can you come back tomorrow?
0100000009	Would you like a cup of tea?
0100000010	Was that what you were talking about?
0100000011	Did you catch my drift?
0100000012	Is that your final decision?
0100000013	Did you tell them where we'd be?
0100000014	Was it the right one?
0100000015	Can I hear that again?
0100000016	Is there anyway I can help?
0100000017	Are you sure of this?
0100000018	Do you want to start?
0100000019	Was it what you expected?
0100000020	Can you wait a moment please?
0100000021	Am I allowed to come with you?
0100000022	Will you tell me please?
0100000023	May I tell you something?
0100000024	Was it empty or full?
0100000025	Shall we do it anyways?
0100000026	Will you wait a moment?
0100000027	Do you understand what I mean?
0100000028	Are you sure that's what they meant?
0100000029	Is this the last one?
0100000030	Have you met them before?
0100000031	Shall we take a rest?
0100000032	Did you see them before you left?
0100000033	May I ask a question?
0100000034	Is there anything I can do?
0100000035	May I offer a suggestion?
0100000036	When did you arrive last night?
0100000037	Where shall we have lunch?
0100000038	Do you want to eat outside today?
0100000039	Could you please take it away from here?
0100000040	How long have you been living there?
0100000041	Why do you think that?
0100000042	It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
0100000043	How can I help you?
0100000044	How long have you been waiting?
0100000045	How far away is it?
0100000046	The place is beautiful, isn't it?
0100000047	What are you talking about?
0100000048	Is that the new doctor?
0100000049	When will you see him?
0100000050	What time will we meet?
0100000051	What is the point of that poster?
0100000052	What is the total weight?
0100000053	Where's the best place to eat?
0100000054	How did you find me?
0100000055	What is the expiration date?
0100000056	Who did she talk to last?
0100000057	What is the temperature today?
0100000058	How come it's not today?
0100000059	What was the secret menu item?
0100000060	Why wasn't the stove turned off?
0100000061	Where's the nearest post office?
0100000062	What color should I choose?
0100000063	Why wasn't the door locked?
0100000064	What time does the film finish?
0100000065	When is it convenient for you to come over?
0100000066	Where will you be on Saturday?
0100000067	When did you get here?
0100000068	How old is your daughter?
0100000069	When will you go to China?
0100000070	Where did you find it?
0100000071	What was the final price?
0100000072	When does the show end?
0100000073	Where is the parking deck located?
0100000074	Who borrowed my phone charger?
0100000075	When do you get off from school?
0100000076	Why didn't you answer my call?
0100000077	When does the warranty expire?
0100000078	We're having a great time, aren’t we?
0100000079	Where are you going to stay on vacation?
0100000080	How long have you lived in this country?
0100000081	So what will a million or so US dollars get you these days?
0100000082	Does your second-home dream look more like a trendy urban loft apartment than a beachside villa?
0100000083	Did we mention the clawfoot bathtub?
0100000084	Is this our course of action today?
0100000085	Have you purchased a home abroad?
0100000086	Do you think this violin belonged to your grandfather?
0100000087	What kind of unforeseen adventures has it sparked?
0100000088	How did you decide on the location?
0100000089	What is your name and location?
0100000090	How can we get in touch?
0100000091	And who can ask for more than that in life?
0100000092	If not, what is the alternative?
0100000093	Once the trash reaches the ocean, where does it all go?
0100000094	Why were no proactive measures being taken on this matter?
0100000095	So what are we missing today?
0100000096	What was your biggest break this year?
0100000097	How can banks convince depositors that their money is safe?
0100000098	Who was the president at that time?
0100000099	Why not make a different point?
0100000100	Who will suffer if it goes wrong?
0200000001	I can't believe you didn't tell me earlier!
0200000002	This dessert is best made a day ahead, to allow the flavours to combine.
0200000003	I dare you to do that again!
0200000004	How's that for a taste of your own medicine!
0200000005	I've have such a long day!
0200000006	That was the most delicious meal I've ever had!
0200000007	He was the one who did it!
0200000008	I am so darn proud of you!
0200000009	Now that's what I call Texas Barbeque!
0200000010	This isn't what you think it is!
0200000011	You won't believe what just happened!
0200000012	Don't blame your problems on others!
0200000013	I'm done playing games with you!
0200000014	Do it again, if you dare!
0200000015	I knew you could do it!
0200000016	I could play better than that!
0200000017	It is scorching hot outside!
0200000018	I am in a hurry right now!
0200000019	It smells like burnt bacon in here!
0200000020	You are only 30 minutes late!
0200000021	You forgot pickles and mustard on my burger!
0200000022	Oh, look who it is!
0200000023	That was the worst idea I've ever heard!
0200000024	Be careful, it's not safe!
0200000025	I didn't know limes were so sour!
0200000026	Only a sucker would believe that story!
0200000027	Help give me a hand!
0200000028	I knew I shouldn't have come along!
0200000029	I love you so much!
0200000030	I wish you the very best!
0200000031	Let me get dressed first!
0200000032	It was the greatest feeling ever!
0200000033	That is such a noble accomplishment!
0200000034	I am so proud of you!
0200000035	Wait for me, I am coming too!
0200000036	That was such a good deal!
0200000037	I couldn't help but smiling ear to ear!
0200000038	That's a trip of a lifetime!
0200000039	I feel so relaxed and refreshed!
0200000040	I am getting a new car next week!
0200000041	Don't forget to feed the dogs!
0200000042	I'm not happy at all!
0200000043	It was so hot and humid in Miami!
0200000044	Let me out of here!
0200000045	There's not I can do about it!
0200000046	I can't wait for graduation!
0200000047	I am getting off school early today!
0200000048	Those buffalo wings were extremely spicy!
0200000049	Please don't tell my mom!
0200000050	I cannot for the life of me leave any recipe alone!
0200000051	An impressive meal that comes together mostly with what you probably have on hand!
0200000052	I feel like a million bucks right now!
0200000053	Wait, I left my keys in the car!
0200000054	Keep you eyes on the road!
0200000055	The sky was very beautiful today!
0200000056	I told you, I'm not interested!
0200000057	You don't need to keep reminding me, I already know!
0200000058	I never want to leave this place!
0200000059	Don't you tell me what to do!
0200000060	I can't even reach the pedal!
0200000061	I've had such a blast here!
0200000062	That's the best news I've heard all day!
0200000063	Please don't spill the beans on my secret!
0200000064	We can all go together now!
0200000065	How beautiful and historic this city is!
0200000066	Put me down right this second!
0200000067	Why won't you listen to any advice I give you!
0200000068	Stop spreading these rumors around!
0200000069	That peach cobbler was the truth!
0200000070	I got accepted into Georgetown University!
0200000071	I need you to leave town and never come back!
0200000072	You were meant to be back yesterday!
0200000073	The puzzle is driving me up the wall!
0200000074	You scared the life out of me!
0200000075	I'm really going to miss this place!
0200000076	That car was so fast!
0200000077	That was perhaps the greatest game I've ever watched!
0200000078	I am proud to announce I am the father of a baby boy!
0200000079	It was literally the easiest thing I've ever done!
0200000080	We want the prime minister to resign!
0200000081	That massage felt so wonderful!
0200000082	Don't let the door hit you on your way out!
0200000083	We need to evacuate pronto!
0200000084	Now that's a proper pepperoni pizza!
0200000085	Please give a warm welcome to the student body president!
0200000086	Watch out, the floor is very slippery!
0200000087	Take your ribs outside — and your salad and sundae too!
0200000088	I want to talk to your manager, now!
0200000089	Let go of my hair!
0200000090	You wouldn't believe who I just ran into!
0200000091	She was the one who stole my wallet!
0200000092	I love the color of your dress!
0200000093	I want to thank you for a good job!
0200000094	Congrats, you won first place!
0200000095	You should really mind your own business!
0200000096	Maybe you're lifting the cover off your barbecuing beast in your backyard!
0200000097	I am ecstatic to announce I will be attending Vanderbilt University!
0200000098	I nearly fell off the bus!
0200000099	What a terrible day this was for the city of New York!
0200000100	That section sofa is simply gorgeous!
0300000001	I heard the game will be broadcast on N B C.
0300000002	It’s a party where you B Y O B.
0300000003	Thanks for the kind words hun, I'll T T Y L.
0300000004	Will you be going to the U S C game today?
0300000005	He scored a K O victory with a vicious right hand.
0300000006	Logan Paul is a well known K O L.
0300000007	I'll be flying from Chicago to N Y C tonight.
0300000008	He will be making a position change from tight end to O L.
0300000009	You need to take a shower as you have a serious case of B O.
0300000010	The man had to check in with his P O every week.
0300000011	L A is the second largest city in America.
0300000012	Hartsfield Jackson International Airport is abbreviated A T L.
0300000013	Not many kids make it from the college ranks into the N B A.
0300000014	The average N F L player is a millionaire.
0300000015	That Mercedes isn't a normal Mercedes, it's an A M G.
0300000016	He got a job offer from the prestigious consulting firm B C G.
0300000017	He transferred to I M G Academy in Florida.
0300000018	Do you want a milkshake from D Q?
0300000019	That's not how you spell my name, F Y I.
0300000020	Have you used A I G insurance before?
0300000021	The game is going into O T.
0300000022	I heard A M C stock has been soaring this week.
0300000023	All I can say is S M H.
0300000024	C N N headquarters were damaged during the protests.
0300000025	Please tune into the M S N B C YouTube channel for more details.
0300000026	The man is suspected to have died from an O D.
0300000027	The coach called a T O before the half.
0300000028	I think the C K logos adorning the bag are cute.
0300000029	He was accepted into G W University.
0300000030	U W M C stock had a strong buy rating from analysts.
0300000031	The Cardinals of S T L had a strong showing tonight.
0300000032	I need an F A to look over the documents.
0300000033	O M G, did you see the video?
0300000034	I heard F I U has a really good business school.
0300000035	What happened to the A C D C poster you had.
0300000036	I remember watching A F V with the family as a kid.
0300000037	The sinking boat sent out an S O S signal.
0300000038	The firm hired K M P G for the audit.
0300000039	I heard the W W E will be holding in person crowds again at shows.
0300000040	The young boy was diagnosed with A D H D.
0300000041	He earned a master's degree from N E U.
0300000042	I applied for my C C L at the gun store today.
0300000043	He was charged with reckless driving and a D U I.
0300000044	I got my P M P certificate yesterday.
0300000045	I think Nvidia's biggest competitor is A M D.
0300000046	Do you remember the days when we used A O L.
0300000047	I scored really high on my G R E.
0300000048	Deliver the goods with a B O L attached.
0300000049	I will be majoring in C S.
0300000050	I think there is something wrong with the S D card.