0000000001	The IEA, originally established to deal with the 1970s oil shock by expanding supply, is now laying out a pathway to a zero emissions future, without any coal or gas.
0000000002	The MBA said in the first four months of 2021, there were 145 building and construction insolvencies in Victoria — up 34.3 per cent on the same time last year.
0000000003	One of the issues that led to the leadership spill was ongoing disquiet in the Nationals about the Prime Minister's increasing support of a net zero by 2050 emissions target.
0000000004	Following recent advice from the AHPPC, which includes limiting international arrivals nationally, Western Australia will be capping its international arrivals at 512 a week, down from 1025.
0000000005	The Gold Coast's surging property market and dwindling vacancy rates have "overwhelmed" crisis accommodation, with one charity struggling to find rental properties for those facing homelessness or escaping domestic violence.
0000000006	Once potatoes are grilled, toss with remaining olive oil, chopped cilantro, rasped or minced garlic, lemon juice and zest and salt and pepper.
0000000007	The National Farmers' Federation and the Backpacker and Youth Tourism Advisory Panel are framing a proposal that would initially allow 150 backpackers to travel to Australia, as soon as October.
0000000008	He said the NFF was working with the Backpacker Youth Tourism Advisory Panel to develop "a COVID-safe pathway proposal" that would allow backpackers into Australia in a "highly controlled manner".
0000000009	But the nearly one in five parents who worried that their child was behind in hitting milestones didn't seek advice from a professional.
0000000010	They fight for residual programs such as drought support or regional funding that are limited in scope, time and impact and subject to considerable criticism as to effectiveness and fairness.
0000000011	They likely have followed your child for a while and can pick up on the individual nuances of your unique child. 
0000000012	A new study puts to rest the fear that your daily fuel will cause heart palpitations -- or cardiac arrhythmia, as doctors call it.
0000000013	Meanwhile, Health Secretary Matt Hancock said that he hoped to bring in a new approach to self-isolation to reflect the changing situation as the country opens up more and more.
0000000014	People with a fully functioning gene -- which can be affected by lifestyle habits such as smoking -- metabolize coffee at a normal rate. 
0000000015	But when that gene mutates, the rate at which the body metabolizes coffee might slow down, and the coffee high could last longer or be felt at a greater rate.
0000000016	As well as dwellings, the proposal would also introduce comprehensive planting to strengthen all boundaries and ensure the next generation of mature trees and hedgerows will flourish on the site.
0000000017	In its genetic analysis, the study did not find any significant association between an impaired coffee metabolism and arrhythmia risk.
0000000018	Today, science has a different view. In fact, a "review of 201 meta-analyses found that moderate consumption of coffee is likely more beneficial than harmful to health," Marcus wrote.
0000000019	Steward volunteers support with the efficient and safe movement of patients through all vaccination sites, ensuring that social distancing measures are in place and identifying people who require additional support.
0000000020	Also, a number of "possible health benefits of caffeine and coffee in particular have emerged, such as reduction in cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular disease and overall mortality," according to the study.
0000000021	Eating at least three servings of whole grains each day can keep your weight, blood pressure and blood sugar levels in check as you age, a new study found.
0000000022	"These data suggest that people who eat more whole grains are better able to maintain their blood sugar and blood pressure over time," McKeown said.
0000000023	A single serving of whole grains is one slice of whole-grain bread, or a half cup of oats, or a half cup of brown rice.
0000000024	Eating the whole grain, as our ancestors used to do, provides a host of benefits to the body that are lost when the grain is processed.
0000000025	Teenagers who have close, secure relationships with their families are more likely to extend empathy to their peers, according to a new study.
0000000026	With a background in naval architecture and ocean engineering, Ehrhorn, who is from Germany, first conceived the Bubble Barrier when he spent a semester abroad in Australia, studying environmental engineering.
0000000027	More specifically, when teens feel safe, supported by and connected to parents or other adult caregivers, they are better equipped to pass the empathy they receive on to others.
0000000028	The flour in white breads, bagels, pastries and pasta has lost the grain's fibber-rich outer layer during the refining process. 
0000000029	Also lost is the inner germ layer that's full of antioxidants, magnesium, potassium, vitamin B and healthy fats.
0000000030	Stern's work revolves around how having secure relationships contributes to prosocial behaviour, or behaviour driven by the intent to benefit others.
0000000031	Britain's fourth biggest supermarket chain Morrisons has become the takeover target of an American private equity firm in the latest sign of a strong appetite among investors for UK assets.
0000000032	In 1947, two years after the war had ended, the Queen used clothing ration coupons to purchase all her wedding dress -- a common practice for brides at the time.
0000000033	Researchers paid attention not only to what the teens said, but also how they articulated it.
0000000034	After these initial interviews, researchers went back to the participants at ages 16, 17 and 18 and observed their interactions with a close friend. 
0000000035	Police carried out regular checks on departing travellers at the island's Olbia Costa Smeralda Airport, as well as on various e-commerce sites where the sand was being sold, they added.
0000000036	Small incremental changes in your diet to increase whole-grain intake will make a difference over time.
0000000037	The researchers noted how the participants responded when their friend presented a problem and confided in them, assessing the participants' extension of empathy.
0000000038	Teens who had more secure family relationships showed higher empathy toward their friends at ages 16 and 17 than less secure teens.
0000000039	Lake Powell and nearby Lake Mead, the nation's largest reservoir, have drained at an alarming rate this year.
0000000040	In the US and Europe, ancient grains like protein-rich quinoa, farro and amaranth have been growing in popularity for the past decade and a half.
0000000041	Pair your cheese and charcuterie with a peachy drink. Peach lemonade can be served on its own or spiked with vodka or rum.
0000000042	In addition to enjoying them raw and cooked in desserts, fresh peaches can be roasted, pickled, and even frozen for a burst of summer sunshine in the middle of winter.
0000000043	These grains have remained largely unchanged over the past several hundred years, according to the Whole Grains Council.
0000000044	Less commonly known ancient grains include iron-rich teff, which has a distinctive nutty flavour but can be pricier than more common grains like oats. 
0000000045	Here's how you can maximize your peach perfection with recipe ideas for breakfast, lunch, dinner -- and dessert, of course.
0000000046	It's not all bad news, though, because the less secure teens "caught up" in their empathic behaviour by age 18, to Stern's surprise.
0000000047	Overnight oats are a trend that's not going away anytime soon, and summer is the ideal time to embrace this chilled-out breakfast dish. 
0000000048	This is cause for hope, she said, because it may indicate that those empathic skills can develop over time for adolescents who don't have great relationships at home. 
0000000049	You can experiment with these grains by incorporating them in small amounts into your morning bowl of oatmeal.
0000000050	This easily adaptable recipe can be made vegan with your choice of plant-based yogurt and milk, or with any combination of dairy that suits you.
0000000051	Add fresh sliced peaches to a mason jar with oats, milk and spices, and you've got a sweet peach cobbler-inspired treat waiting for you in the morning.
0000000052	Fire up the grill and give your peaches a little heat to turn them into a sweetly charred accompaniment for a number of dishes.
0000000053	It's hard to deny that tomatoes are the ideal summer food -- and that's saying a lot in a season where so much produce is at its peak. 
0000000054	But when a heat wave strikes, as one has throughout much of the United States over the past few weeks, the tomato really proves its worth.
0000000055	To grill peaches, preheat a gas or charcoal grill to medium heat. Halve and pit the peaches, then brush the cut halves with olive oil or vegetable oil.
0000000056	Though cooking tomatoes does boost their lycopene content, you'll still get enough from an uncooked tomato to make it worth your while, according to Manganiello. 
0000000057	If you really want to help up your antioxidant intake, add a little bit of olive oil.
0000000058	Place cut-side down and cook uncovered for 4 to 5 minutes, until grill marks appear and the peaches release easily from the grill grates.
0000000059	Stern suggested that having strong friendships or a trusted teacher might make an impact on insecure teens' empathy, but she said further research should be done to learn more.
0000000060	Grilled peaches become the star of the show in a big salad, like this quinoa, peach and summer vegetable salad that works as a main course. 
0000000061	Currently, all people arriving in the UK from a country on the government's amber list must quarantine for 10 days - regardless of whether they have had a coronavirus jab.
0000000062	"Consuming fresh tomatoes with a source of fat, such as olive oil, is a great way to boost lycopene absorption," she said.
0000000063	Southerners rave over the simplicity of a tomato sandwich on white bread, dressed lightly with mayonnaise and salt. 
0000000064	When it comes down to it, almost anything can be a salad or a sandwich -- the potential combinations are endless. 
0000000065	And if you want to pile on more ingredients, you'll find ways to make a tomato sandwich every day of the week.
0000000066	Swap out the mayonnaise for hummus, ranch dressing, cream cheese or spicy mustard. Add a sliced hard-boiled egg or avocado.
0000000067	Or simply drizzle them with balsamic vinegar and quality olive oil along with a sprinkling of flaky sea salt and serve as a fruit salad.
0000000068	Grab extra napkins for the juicy mess of cherry pepper relish or pickled onions. Or if you're in the mood for classic comfort, there's always the BLT.
0000000069	An outdoor happy hour is always happier with a special cocktail for sipping and a grazing board for snacking.
0000000070	Layer slices of fresh peaches or watermelon with tomatoes, mozzarella and basil on your salad platter, or for a kid-friendly twist, make caprese skewers.
0000000071	Turn it into the base for a Cobb salad with as many tomatoes and leftover fridge elements as you can handle. 
0000000072	Monday's results saw Ukraine and Finland finish third in their respective groups on three points apiece, meaning that if England did slip to that place they would still go through.
0000000073	Try this recipe as a start, and pick and choose add-ins like roasted red peppers and marinated chickpeas to suit your tastes.
0000000074	We all love slow-simmered marinara sauce for ladling over pasta, but the heat of July might not be the best time to cook up a big batch.
0000000075	Instead, stir up a no-cook tomato sauce that practically explodes with the juiciness of fresh tomatoes.
0000000076	The word "pesto" seems synonymous with basil, but tomatoes can find their way into this rustic sauce, too.
0000000077	Inappropriate laughter can sometimes be a sign that something is cognitively amiss. 
0000000078	He has again insisted that neither a lack of fitness nor speculation over his club future are the reasons for his lack of goals against Croatia and Scotland at Wembley.
0000000079	He has frequently insisted that neither a lack of fitness nor speculation over his club future are the reasons for his lack of goals against Croatia and Scotland at Wembley.
0000000080	Pickled peaches are a piquant complement to soft cheeses like fresh goat, Brie or Taleggio, which in turn taste fantastic with cured meats like prosciutto and speck.
0000000081	Either of these sauces also works well as a bruschetta and crostini topping for an impromptu happy hour with snacks.
0000000082	The results suggest that, in order to raise an empathic adolescent, parents need to model and encourage empathy.
0000000083	Since the research focused on averages across the study sample, she also said an examination of individual differences between participants is necessary.
0000000084	If you can't stand the heat, get out of the kitchen and fire up the grill.
0000000085	You won't have to spend much time over the flame, but if you want a hot meal on a hot day, grilled dishes with tomatoes fit the bill.
0000000086	Foil packet meals are quite possibly the easiest way to grill with very little mess and clean-up.
0000000087	Travelers in need of a digital detox, or just an escape from the stresses of recent times, will relish being marooned for a few days in this hard-to-reach tropical island.
0000000088	Place salmon fillets on a piece of heavy-duty foil drizzled with olive oil and load them up with halved cherry tomatoes and herbs like rosemary, dill or cilantro.
0000000089	This method is infinitely versatile -- so if you're craving other seafood, like shrimp or scallops, or more summer vegetables, you can customize it to each family member's tastes.
0000000090	Brian Cook, who had participated in the run and photographed the royal trio, sharing the snap on Twitter, said it was a "nice surprise, and nice of them to do".
0000000091	If chips and salsa are all you have an appetite for, make homemade salsa by charring whole tomatoes, peppers and onions on the grill. 
0000000092	For parents and even teachers, Stern advises understanding the necessity of empathy and really investing in relationships with teens. 
0000000093	A few minutes are enough to blister their skins and boost the flavour of the blend.
0000000094	Tomato water can be used in martinis and Bloody Marys or mixed with gin or vodka and tonic.
0000000095	Meanwhile, Dr Susan Hopkins, Public Health England's director for COVID-19, warned "we may have to do further lockdowns this winter" depending on whether hospitals start to become overwhelmed or not.
0000000096	Tomato water is nothing more than the slowly -- very slowly -- strained liquid from a tomato, and it's a low-maintenance way to make stellar drinks.
0000000097	Line a metal strainer with a flour sack towel or cheesecloth, then place it over a deep bowl.
0000000098	Chop tomatoes and sprinkle with salt, then pour into the towel and refrigerate for at least eight and up to 24 hours.
0000000099	There should be equipment stored close to the pool so that if someone begins drowning, it's at the ready for the person to grab on to for safety, she said.
0000000100	Prof Wren said it was "very encouraging" that more than 700,000 vaccine appointments were booked on the day that jabs became available to people aged 18 to 20 in England.
0000000101	We owe that notion to a comic-strip cartoonist named Elzie Crisler Segar, who created a character that he based on a rough-edged, hard-drinking local from his Illinois hometown.
0000000102	By 1933, when he began to appear as one of the lead characters in an animated cartoon series called "Thimble Theatre," Popeye was getting instant strength from spinach.
0000000103	These nitrates are rapidly depleted during exercise or physical exertion and replenishing them "increases force production in exercising skeletal muscle.
0000000104	"More research is being done now to determine if increased nitrate in muscle translates to increase muscle strength and improved athletic performance," Hord added.
0000000105	This jibes well with Hord's observation that spinach contains plenty of vitamin K, which helps lower blood pressure and the risk of cardiovascular disease.
0000000106	Unless it's cooked beyond recognition, spinach is also a good source of vitamin C. It has no cholesterol or fat.
0000000107	Harold McGee, the dean of culinary science, argued that there are better sources of strength-building minerals. 
0000000108	Though the iron of the pumping-iron set isn't what McGee means, it's iron that you want for sculpting bulging biceps and an admirable six-pack.
0000000109	Spinach has plenty of lutein, which is believed to support eye health and reduce the incidence of macular degeneration, a concern mostly of people 55 or older. 
0000000110	Leafy greens of many kinds, including cruciferous vegetables such as broccoli and bok choy, are known to inhibit heart disease and stroke, as well as certain cancers.
0000000111	Spinach joins these, with the greatest benefits derived from these vegetables in their raw or lightly cooked form.
0000000112	Finally, a diet that includes green leafy vegetables such as spinach, kale and greens, containing all the good things that Al Bochi noted, seems to help slow cognitive decline.
0000000113	Even with all its potential, Popeye's favourite food does have a few downsides. Spinach, especially raw spinach, can lend some people a, well, gassy air.
0000000114	"Too much of any food is not healthy," Hord said. "Spinach contains oxalic acid, which may bind minerals in the diet, like calcium, and render them unavailable for absorption."
0000000115	The tickets are paperless and passengers can use the updated season ticket calculator on the National Rail website to find out the best ticket for their route and travel patterns.
0000000116	If you're concerned about getting enough calcium in your system, it may be well to leave spinach out of the cheesy lasagnes in which it is so often deployed. 
0000000117	Too much oxalic acid is also a recipe for kidney stones, and therefore, Hord added, "this may negatively affect people" who are susceptible to them.
0000000118	All due respect to Popeye, a can may not be the tastiest way to introduce it to your table. 
0000000119	This is usually fine -- just remember that spinach can be a good vehicle for E. coli, Listeria and other harmful bacteria and germs.
0000000120	For this reason, the US Centres for Disease Control and Prevention recommends that spinach be cooked at 160º for 15 seconds, which kills potentially fatal bacteria.
0000000121	Lightly sautéing fresh spinach in a drizzle of olive or avocado oil meets this baseline, and it's tasty and nutritious as well.
0000000122	Another option is to wash spinach and other leafy greens thoroughly in running water before eating them.
0000000123	Adults should also encourage teens to invest in their relationships with their friends, which the study found helps build empathy as a skill as well, Stern said.
0000000124	Drinking up to three or four cups of caffeinated or decaffeinated coffee a day reduces your risk of developing and dying from chronic liver diseases, a new study found.
0000000125	"This would be especially valuable in countries with lower income and worse access to healthcare and where the burden of chronic liver disease is highest," Kennedy said.
0000000126	An early sign of dementia is an altered sense of humour and laughing at inappropriate moments, one study found.
0000000127	The rate of liver cancer has more than tripled between 1980 and today, "while the death rates have more than doubled," according to the American Cancer Society.
0000000128	Researchers followed a group of 9,000 children, who were taking part in a wider study, from the age of 7 to 24. 
0000000129	Food diaries were completed at age 7, 10 and 13, recording the food and drinks children consumed over three days.
0000000130	Measurements of body mass index, weight, waist circumference and body fat were also collected over the study period.
0000000131	The children were divided in five groups based on how much ultra-processed food they ate.
0000000132	In the lowest group, ultra-processed foods accounted for one fifth of their total diet, while in the highest group they accounted for more than two-thirds.
0000000133	However, she added, whom teenagers decide to befriend does matter.
0000000134	While the study shows a link between eating ultra processed foods and increases in BMI and body fat, it doesn't definitively show cause and effect.
0000000135	Previous studies on the same issue had yielded inconsistent findings but they involved fewer children and short follow-up periods, the researchers said.
0000000136	According to the researchers, more radical and effective measures are needed to reduce children's exposure and consumption of ultra-processed foods.
0000000137	For thousands of years, we've used one vegetable as a spice to flavour our toast, treat ear infections and ward off vampires: garlic.
0000000138	Garlic is the edible bulb of a plant in the lily family, native to central Asia.
0000000139	In addition to making food taste better, it has traditionally been used for health purposes by cultures such as the Egyptians, Greeks, Romans, Chinese and Japanese.
0000000140	The blood disorder porphyria may have supported this belief, according to the Carnegie Museum of Natural History. 
0000000141	A total of 7,723 new cases and 134 hospital admissions were found to have the Delta variant, which is thought to be about 60% more transmissible than the Alpha variant.
0000000142	It was found that while vaccines reduced the risk of being admitted to hospital, strong effects against the Delta variant were not seen until 28 days after the first jab.
0000000143	It's hard to separate the benefits of laughter and the context in which you would laugh.
0000000144	Allicin is also the compound to which most potential health benefits attributed to garlic have been credited. 
0000000145	Everyone likes a good belly laugh from time to time, and science supports that feeling.
0000000146	Studies have shown that laughing is linked to our physical, emotional and mental well-being -- even our relationships.
0000000147	Laughter is thought to have evolved as a form of social bonding in animals and as a way to express playful intention. 
0000000148	But humans don't need a physical trigger to laugh -- though generally we can't help but laugh if we're tickled.
0000000149	Janet Gibson, a professor emerita of cognitive psychology at Grinnell College in Iowa, said that laughter evolved in humans as a communication signal.
0000000150	A four-week-long study of employees of a car battery plant found that garlic reduced blood lead levels by 19%.
0000000151	More than 6,000 people were made homeless.
0000000152	The Aussie dollar has lifted slightly to 72.
0000000153	A screenshot from a Trivago TV ad in December 2017.
0000000154	They are now throwing them into the air and twirling them around the body.
0000000155	Some use bright, flashing hoops.
0000000156	Australia’s population officially ticked above 25 million last night.
0000000157	One in 200 people are homeless, according to Homelessness Australia.
0000000158	Camels have been here in Australia since mid 1800s.
0000000159	The things I learned created constellations of fascination.
0000000160	Somewhere, there is a photo of me with my arms thrown around his neck.
0000000161	They say the things we love as children stay with us.
0000000162	Others use multiple hoops at the same time.
0000000163	It was a movement mediation that I needed during that time in my life.
0000000164	Then over time it just followed me everywhere I went.
0000000165	For about the 1000th time, this is a national competition.
0000000166	He also admitted he may not be at the Broncos in 2019.
0000000167	Around 26,000 households are randomly selected to complete the LFS each month.
0000000168	I was going to different cities, and I was bringing my hoops.
0000000169	My wife and I are aged 65 and 64 respectively.
0000000170	My hoops were getting smaller.
0000000171	But new research suggests these creatures weren't exactly thriving before that fateful strike.
0000000172	I just put my phone up and dance to a goofy popular song.
0000000173	Stakeholders can lodge submissions to the Treasury website until 27 September.
0000000174	That changed on July 28.
0000000175	Hurricane Katrina hit America’s south in 2005.
0000000176	Earlier this week, Australia’s population ticked over the 25 million mark.
0000000177	The bull market in US shares has reached 3,453 days.
0000000178	But many are struggling to make sure the 2030 targets are met.
0000000179	The black 2015 BMW X6  has the Queensland registration 9I9.
0000000180	Spence built and renovated a few places before we met in 2010.
0000000181	Companies selling hoops have reported an increase in demand.
0000000182	Mid winter sessions last up to 20 minutes.
0000000183	Human Nature are back in Australia ahead of their tour in 2019.
0000000184	A 26-year-old Launceston man was charged on Tuesday afternoon.
0000000185	More than 20 trucks are currently on the scene on Somerville Road.
0000000186	About 200 graduates a year are needed.
0000000187	The report is based a survey of 722 organisations across Australia.
0000000188	And we only have the athletes 30 per cent of the time.
0000000189	The company has trained more than 1100 submariners since 1993.
0000000190	Coles has 800 large stores in terrific locations.
0000000191	Sweepers checked the area and an 1100 metre exclusion zone was set up.
0000000192	Children will enjoy playing on the 1047 square metre block.
0000000193	Connie is 6 and Reggie is 5.
0000000194	Nine is yet to confirm the show for 2019.
0000000195	Scientists studied 1,600 dinosaur fossils, representing 247 species, to track their evolution.
0000000196	Imagine Pac-Man, but on an astronomical scale. 
0000000197	The egg weighs 170g, is 80mm long and 65mm wide.
0000000198	The September 2018 Astrology is surprisingly good.
0000000199	The legislation comes into effect on August 15.
0000000200	Scientists also discovered a new type of supernova this week.
0000000201	It feels like we’re going backwards 230 years.
0000000202	In 2018, the Mendelsohn Student Lecture will again take place.
0000000203	The Duncan incident was in 2007.
0000000204	But the last plan, adopted in 2011, is already seven years old.
0000000205	Submissions close on October 19.
0000000206	But the Tigers are clearly a step ahead in 2018.
0000000207	The shortlists have been announced for the 2018 Inky Awards.
0000000208	The insurance company’s shares fell as much as 26.
0000000209	Take these responses from girls aged between 13 and 15.
0000000210	2001 turned out to be an episode of Getaway.
0000000211	The findings from both discoveries could help scientists unlock secrets of the universe.
0000000212	The company was sold to Proton in 1996.
0000000213	A heat dome over the area, courtesy of our changing climate.
0000000214	Local media reported that 25 people were injured.
0000000215	That could be a really important factor in how we understand relationships.
0000000216	But the intrepid mice persisted on a single island in Shark Bay.
0000000217	The brokenness goes back to the leadership spill of 2015.
0000000218	Over the course of the year, he put up 26.
0000000219	Some 2,000 fans turned up to watch.
0000000220	Google published the summer job sagas of 20 of their top leaders.
0000000221	It all started on Christmas morning, 2016.
0000000222	It appears to be 90% cat hair and 10% red wine stains.
0000000223	Commercially, scarcity of supply beyond 2020 remains a strong market driver.
0000000224	Officials will also want an update on his plans post-2019.
0000000225	Another 1,447 people have been injured and 165,003 displaced.
0000000226	Season 2019 is no different.
0000000227	There are three types of hooping trending right now.
0000000228	As of 11am, the hurricane was about 460 kilometres south of Honolulu.
0000000229	By the end of the 20th century about 40% were professionals.
0000000230	The version you're used to doing as a child is called on-body.
0000000231	That nation relies on nearly 100 percent renewable energy for its production.
0000000232	It involves tossing, flipping and catching the hoop. 
0000000233	Our 2018 Financial Year Online Checklist is currently being released in stages.
0000000234	May future generations of these mice enjoy their island paradises.
0000000235	The Pickers last played finals in 2012 after winning back-to-back titles.
0000000236	Successful cities of the 21st century will need to nurture innovative businesses.
0000000237	In those 17 years, 400,000 asylum seekers were resettled.
0000000238	Beating heart cells were sent to space.
0000000239	Finally, there is weighted hooping. 
0000000240	The majority of our patients are under 10 years old.
0000000241	The bid allows for a distribution to shareholders of another 24 cents a share.
0000000242	Meet the world's oldest known plague victim. 
0000000243	His matter is due before Central Local Court on October 24.
0000000244	Geotechnical investigations will be underway between 2019 and 2021.
0000000245	The patron, who suffers from cerebral palsy, was celebrating her 21st birthday.
0000000246	It opens on Thursday, August 23 in over 220 screens.
0000000247	But he soon backtracked and the summit went ahead on June 12.
0000000248	What happened next could lead to a revolutionary way of helping heart patients.
0000000249	In Australia beer consumption has been falling steadily and dramatically since 1971.
0000000250	These hoops are large and can weigh up to 4 pounds.
0000000251	I did that for about 16 years.
0000000252	My cat is now 78 per cent less of a jerk.
0000000253	In Nantucket, Massachusetts, the plastic orbs were outlawed in 2015.
0000000254	Nominations are open until 5pm on Friday, November 30, 2018.
0000000255	There is no possible doubt that the property is facing ascertained danger.
0000000256	Murray Island was annexed by the Queensland colonial administration in 1879.
0000000257	Art of Science 2018 is held in concurrence with National Science Week.
0000000258	But the Australian government has strongly objected to UNESCO's conclusion.
0000000259	Weighted hoops are used as a fitness routine to strengthen abdominal muscles.
0000000260	The crew donned oxygen and descended to 20,000 feet.
0000000261	Australia is currently part of the 21-country rotating committee.
0000000262	But in 2019 we are going to do something different.
0000000263	Since 1944, 3,325 South Australian babies have been named Brenton.
0000000264	One is the 28 Degrees Mastercard, which also has no annual fee.
0000000265	All up, more then 5000 people participated, half of them students.
0000000266	About 1300 officers took part in the survey.
0000000267	These hoops are designed to stay around your waist.
0000000268	The development revives a concept first proposed in 2012.
0000000269	Beaumont is located approximately 670 kilometres south of Perth.
0000000270	Santas uses it as part of her interval training and warm-up routines.
0000000271	But just 20 kilometres south of Port Augusta something went wrong.
0000000272	21 Lessons for the 21st Century explores the present.
0000000273	More than 120 firefighters are battling the fire on Somerville Road.
0000000274	The bizarre incident occurred about 2am Tuesday, August 14.
0000000275	The legendary Australian promoter last brought the legend to Australia in 2014.
0000000276	The prize was a dollar coin and a 50-cent coin.
0000000277	Hooping was a way for me to get out of my head.
0000000278	Botha counts almost 50 years in the diamond industry.
0000000279	It hasn’t resided on Australian soil since 2002.
0000000280	Saturday night at the SCG, the Swans and Magpies drew 38,000 people.
0000000281	The current 26 is at least six rounds too many.
0000000282	It was opened in three stages from September 2016.
0000000283	6% came in at or below the APS level 4 in 2016-17.
0000000284	It would simply not have been credible not to alert the international community about the situation.
0000000285	For Presnell, the biggest benefit has been self-expression. 
0000000286	On August 17 the VC launched a surprise attack on the base.
0000000287	As a queer woman, hooping is a way to freely express herself through meaningful movements.
0000000288	It was deconsecrated in 1993, and purchased by the community around 2013.
0000000289	The sharemarket fell 60 points or nearly 1 per cent to 6284.
0000000290	30 per cent of Australian girls between 12 and 14 play netball.
0000000291	Presnell also loves the growing community. 
0000000292	That’s a record 22 months in a row of no changes.
0000000293	Five years later, 1600 remain.
0000000294	She describes it as welcoming, loving and embracing of diversity.
0000000295	The last time the Crows truly struggled was 1995 and 1996.
0000000296	A 26-year-old man and a 25-year-old woman, from Riverside, are assisting police.
0000000297	The index is now at the lowest level since January 28, 2016.
0000000298	Currently Australians have 70,000 different products to choose from.
0000000299	Currently there are around 90,000 farmers in this nation.
0000000300	He tied for 17th at the Masters, second at the U.S. Open.
0100000001	Did you not hear what I said?
0100000002	Am I allowed to say something?
0100000003	Where Do The Richest Americans Live?
0100000004	Is this the last of them?
0100000005	Can you pass me the salt?
0100000006	9 Out of 10 Baby Boomers Fail This Quiz, Will You?
0100000007	Is there nothing I can say to change your mind?
0100000008	How much do I need to sleep?
0100000009	Is this our course of action today?
0100000010	Scientifically speaking, what is the purpose of laughter?
0100000011	Do you know what I mean?
0100000012	When does the meeting start?
0100000013	Can you come back tomorrow?
0100000014	Would you like a cup of tea?
0100000015	Was that what you were talking about?
0100000016	How might it help us get back to “normal” as we emerge from the pandemic?
0100000017	Did you catch my drift?
0100000018	Is that your final decision?
0100000019	Did you tell them where we'd be?
0100000020	You're a pilot, aren't you?
0100000021	Was it the right one?
0100000022	Can I hear that again?
0100000023	Why is a plastic knife 10 cents on the dollar to a fully compostable, biodegradable one?
0100000024	Is there anyway I can help?
0100000025	Does spinach make you strong?
0100000026	Are you sure of this?
0100000027	Do you want to start?
0100000028	Was it what you expected?
0100000029	Can you wait a moment please?
0100000030	Am I allowed to come with you?
0100000031	Will you tell me please?
0100000032	May I tell you something?
0100000033	Was it empty or full?
0100000034	Shall we do it anyways?
0100000035	Will you wait a moment?
0100000036	Do you understand what I mean?
0100000037	Now, with all these provisos in mind, what's the best way to put spinach to work?
0100000038	Are you sure that's what they meant?
0100000039	Were they open at 10 am?
0100000040	What Do These Interior Designer Profiles Mean?
0100000041	9/10 People Fail This Movie Quiz, Can you pass?
0100000042	Is this the last one?
0100000043	Have you met them before?
0100000044	Shall we take a rest?
0100000045	Have you got personal experience of it?
0100000046	Did you see them before you left?
0100000047	May I ask a question?
0100000048	Is there anything I can do?
0100000049	May I offer a suggestion?
0100000050	I've have such a long day!
0100000051	When did you arrive last night?
0100000052	Where shall we have lunch?
0100000053	Why is it so important for our brains and well-being?
0100000054	How long have you been living there?
0100000055	Why do you think that?
0100000056	It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
0100000057	How can I help you?
0100000058	How long have you been waiting?
0100000059	How far away is it?
0100000060	The place is beautiful, isn't it?
0100000061	What are you talking about?
0100000062	And who can ask for more than that in life?
0100000063	If not, what is the alternative?
0100000064	Once the trash reaches the ocean, where does it all go?
0100000065	Why were no proactive measures being taken on this matter?
0100000066	So what are we missing today?
0100000067	What was your biggest break this year?
0100000068	How can banks convince depositors that their money is safe?
0100000069	What would happen to my kids if I was jailed?
0100000070	Who was the president at that time?
0100000071	What can the special counsel investigate?
0100000072	Why not make a different point?
0100000073	Who will suffer if it goes wrong?
0100000074	What is wrong in shaking hands with someone for courtesy sake?
0100000075	What does a panic attack feel like?
0100000076	How can I survive somewhere where I have no one?
0100000077	How do we make it stop?
0100000078	And how long will he be allowed to go on?
0100000079	How has demand for home loans been in this year so far?
0100000080	Where do you stand on this issue?
0100000081	The question is what are you going to do about it?
0100000082	So, why does the pro peloton still favour tubulars?
0100000083	What might you be worrying about?
0100000084	How much longer should I expect to wait?
0100000085	What happened to that girl?
0100000086	Why would I just walk away and be left jobless?
0100000087	What just happened to our system?
0100000088	If someone were to say, whose is that?
0100000089	How should a prospect move regarding this?
0100000090	What happened to winning at all costs?
0100000091	Is his attitude good or not good?
0100000092	What do you mean by this?
0100000093	Even if you cancel it, how does it help the country?
0100000094	What policies will ensure they go to local people?
0100000095	What about all my male friends?
0100000096	What can I say about his motivation?
0100000097	What’s the best way to improve communication between healthcare professionals and patients?
0100000098	But what about the protocols that govern those interactions?
0100000099	What are the survival statistics for cervical cancer?
0100000100	Did you drink that milk?
0200000001	If it feels warm and dry then water away!
0200000002	Have your say and cast your vote for the 2018 Logies now!
0200000003	He’s about the same age as me now!
0200000004	Thank YOU for all your beautiful messages of love and support!
0200000005	I decided to have the pizza!
0200000006	Adults can even join in the fun too!
0200000007	I am now 12 and I have a dream!
0200000008	They’ve been here 50,000 years!
0200000009	I’m shaking at the moment!
0200000010	And I can’t believe him!
0200000011	These videos always get lots of attention and compliments!
0200000012	We love you and we WILL be back!
0200000013	But we know what you really want!
0200000014	Men come in all shapes, sizes, colours and creeds!
0200000015	It would have been rude not to!
0200000016	We heard a loud piercing scream… and a NO!
0200000017	That could be the reason for such savings on the plan!
0200000018	I want to have that outfit!
0200000019	It really is the simple things sometimes!
0200000020	But it was kind of a success!
0200000021	We love showing his students that very first entry!
0200000022	You are a bully and a nasty, typical man!
0200000023	I'm done playing games with you!
0200000024	You also need to find the right partner for that too!
0200000025	He came up to me and asked me to talk!
0200000026	And we thought 2017 was a big year!
0200000027	Allah has answered your request and guided my mother!
0200000028	It looks like a sound and it sounds like a sound!
0200000029	He really wanted that trainer to know he was punched!
0200000030	All of that stuff is made up!
0200000031	And already he’s not ruling out a comeback!
0200000032	Congratulations — you just burned 511 calories!
0200000033	It doesn’t get any better than that!
0200000034	I’ve told him it is supposed to be coming!
0200000035	It is the most beautiful ring I have ever seen!
0200000036	I did this some years ago and it was tremendously liberating!
0200000037	West is in the building!
0200000038	Make sure you do so at the bottom of this story!
0200000039	See you at the fair!
0200000040	If you don't have steel, you don't have a country!
0200000041	This isn’t tipping, it’s a lucky dip!
0200000042	Watch the ten best moments from the Oscars!
0200000043	I knew I shouldn't have come along!
0200000044	Check out their new Link 10 and 20 speakers now!
0200000045	If you’re not this kind of person, that’s okay!
0200000046	He doesn’t understand the meaning of the word full!
0200000047	We are moving to Melbourne!
0200000048	The World is watching and waiting!
0200000049	David’s in the chair and he’s doing a great job!
0200000050	Congrats, you won first place!
0200000051	I knew you could do it!
0200000052	Just wanted to confirm it’s not a thing!
0200000053	It’s available in 900 cities!
0200000054	We want free, fair and SMART TRADE!
0200000055	We’re about to find out!
0200000056	Comey knew it all, and much more!
0200000057	That’s a good one for you!
0200000058	I started when I was about 15!
0200000059	It all adds to it!
0200000060	She did those challenges, not just with courage, but with a grin!
0200000061	Hold on, and off we go!
0200000062	It’s monotonous and I’m sick of it!
0200000063	But we’re Bayern and we’re desperate to reach the final!
0200000064	I mean, they don’t cost that much to buy!
0200000065	Get me out of here!
0200000066	I’ve made vanities and tables from old roof timbers!
0200000067	This is all about respect and it pays off!
0200000068	Sorry, it’s time for change!
0200000069	Come have some fun with two gorgeous girls from Finland and Australia!
0200000070	And then I started shouting, Freedom!
0200000071	May we present to you the ultimate mac and cheese!
0200000072	Be sure to bring your water bottle and hat!
0200000073	I truly appreciate your understanding and sense of humour about this!
0200000074	You have this, and you have that!
0200000075	That doesn’t happen to me!
0200000076	The stats are alarming, and aren’t getting better!
0200000077	You should really mind your own business!
0200000078	Good morning from the final day of the 2018 HD Therapeutics Conference!
0200000079	Some of you have done this and I do thank you!
0200000080	Welcome back ladies and gentlemen!
0200000081	It’s an impressive release that we didn’t think was achievable!
0200000082	I cannot wait to meet with you!
0200000083	I couldn’t have even made that up!
0200000084	He reminded me of that when he joined!
0200000085	It will all work out!
0200000086	This was just one of many photos taken today!
0200000087	I don’t think he was very happy with that!
0200000088	And she brings it in spades!
0200000089	We'll never fear, since the Top 5 is here!
0200000090	If you have the storage space you could save hundreds of dollars!
0200000091	Good luck on your selections this week!
0200000092	Take it straight to the pool or beach from the gym!
0200000093	Only the good bits, that is!
0200000094	Download it NOW for FREE on iOS and Android!
0200000095	The I’m a Celebrity…Get Me Out of Here!
0200000096	And drinking lots and lots of water!
0200000097	White is humble, simple, serene and timeless… just like our summers!
0200000098	The name really says it all here!
0200000099	Thanks to The Canberra Times, at least we have three weeks!
0200000100	I’m going to kiss her all morning!
0300000001	He's heading out to W A next week.
0300000002	Mark was born in N S W but left as a kid.
0300000003	I think that they are being investigated by the A E C.
0300000004	She got a job with the A F P and couldn't be more happy.
0300000005	It feels like the A L P lost their way a long time ago.
0300000006	Does the A M A publish a journal that I can subscribe to?
0300000007	You spell it B R I S B A N E.
0300000008	Is it on A B C or a cable channel?
0300000009	Moving to S A was the best idea that I ever had.
0300000010	I even wrote to the A B S but they couldn't help me.
0300000011	I applied for a job with the D F A T yesterday.
0300000012	Who's the current C E O of Qantas?
0300000013	Do you remember which channel C S I is on?
0300000014	The latest advice from the W H O is a little worrying.
0300000015	She booked an appointment with H R.
0300000016	I try to avoid eating too much K F C.
0300000017	He waited 10 years to be made  C F O.
0300000018	I usually enjoy the international coverage on C N N.
0300000019	I can't remember the last C D that I bought.
0300000020	I haven't visited the M S N site for many years.
0300000021	It's definitely worth picking up on D V D.
0300000022	How long is the flight to the U K?
0300000023	I think the correct spelling is R E S U M E.
0300000024	They want an Australian trade deal after leaving the E U.
0300000025	He deserves the V P position after all that hard work.
0300000026	There's quite a lot of movement between A U D and G B P.
0300000027	Let's head back to H Q and discuss our next move.
0300000028	I first got A D S L in the late nineties.
0300000029	I'm tempted to build my own P C.
0300000030	I don't know if M S N B C is broadcast in Australia.
0300000031	He was her favourite D J.
0300000032	Is that where most of the B B C shows air in Australia?
0300000033	They would have solved it if there had been D N A technology.
0300000034	I believed the scam video about the new G T A game.
0300000035	It didn't look clear enough to be H D.
0300000036	Turn off your router and you should get a new I P address.
0300000037	I will switch I S P if my browsing speed doesn't improve.
0300000038	I enjoy writing H T M L but I need to improve my skills.
0300000039	The E T A hasn't been figured out yet.
0300000040	Send the P D F over tonight and I'll get back to you tomorrow.
0300000041	I keep forgetting to send off for my I D.
0300000042	I want a T V but don't want to spend more than 500 dollars.
0300000043	Is that the finest R P G ever made?
0300000044	His name is Jack A K A Jackie.
0300000045	My B M I is definitely higher than I would like.
0300000046	An F T A could be lucrative for both countries.
0300000047	He got a job in I T because it pays better.
0300000048	The N A A might be able to help you find the document.
0300000049	It's just another poorly regulated N G O.
0300000050	There are some wonderful items in the N M A.