0000000001	A new study puts to rest the fear that your daily fuel will cause heart palpitations -- or cardiac arrhythmia, as doctors call it.
0000000002	Meanwhile, Health Secretary Matt Hancock said that he hoped to bring in a new approach to self-isolation to reflect the changing situation as the country opens up more and more.
0000000003	People with a fully functioning gene -- which can be affected by lifestyle habits such as smoking -- metabolize coffee at a normal rate. 
0000000004	But when that gene mutates, the rate at which the body metabolizes coffee might slow down, and the coffee high could last longer or be felt at a greater rate.
0000000005	As well as dwellings, the proposal would also introduce comprehensive planting to strengthen all boundaries and ensure the next generation of mature trees and hedgerows will flourish on the site.
0000000006	In its genetic analysis, the study did not find any significant association between an impaired coffee metabolism and arrhythmia risk.
0000000007	Today, science has a different view. In fact, a "review of 201 meta-analyses found that moderate consumption of coffee is likely more beneficial than harmful to health," Marcus wrote.
0000000008	Steward volunteers support with the efficient and safe movement of patients through all vaccination sites, ensuring that social distancing measures are in place and identifying people who require additional support.
0000000009	Also, a number of "possible health benefits of caffeine and coffee in particular have emerged, such as reduction in cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular disease and overall mortality," according to the study.
0000000010	Eating at least three servings of whole grains each day can keep your weight, blood pressure and blood sugar levels in check as you age, a new study found.
0000000011	"These data suggest that people who eat more whole grains are better able to maintain their blood sugar and blood pressure over time," McKeown said.
0000000012	A single serving of whole grains is one slice of whole-grain bread, or a half cup of oats, or a half cup of brown rice.
0000000013	Eating the whole grain, as our ancestors used to do, provides a host of benefits to the body that are lost when the grain is processed.
0000000014	Teenagers who have close, secure relationships with their families are more likely to extend empathy to their peers, according to a new study.
0000000015	With a background in naval architecture and ocean engineering, Ehrhorn, who is from Germany, first conceived the Bubble Barrier when he spent a semester abroad in Australia, studying environmental engineering.
0000000016	More specifically, when teens feel safe, supported by and connected to parents or other adult caregivers, they are better equipped to pass the empathy they receive on to others.
0000000017	The flour in white breads, bagels, pastries and pasta has lost the grain's fibber-rich outer layer during the refining process. 
0000000018	Also lost is the inner germ layer that's full of antioxidants, magnesium, potassium, vitamin B and healthy fats.
0000000019	Stern's work revolves around how having secure relationships contributes to prosocial behaviour, or behaviour driven by the intent to benefit others.
0000000020	Britain's fourth biggest supermarket chain Morrisons has become the takeover target of an American private equity firm in the latest sign of a strong appetite among investors for UK assets.
0000000021	In 1947, two years after the war had ended, the Queen used clothing ration coupons to purchase all her wedding dress -- a common practice for brides at the time.
0000000022	Researchers paid attention not only to what the teens said, but also how they articulated it.
0000000023	After these initial interviews, researchers went back to the participants at ages 16, 17 and 18 and observed their interactions with a close friend. 
0000000024	Police carried out regular checks on departing travellers at the island's Olbia Costa Smeralda Airport, as well as on various e-commerce sites where the sand was being sold, they added.
0000000025	Small incremental changes in your diet to increase whole-grain intake will make a difference over time.
0000000026	The researchers noted how the participants responded when their friend presented a problem and confided in them, assessing the participants' extension of empathy.
0000000027	Teens who had more secure family relationships showed higher empathy toward their friends at ages 16 and 17 than less secure teens.
0000000028	Lake Powell and nearby Lake Mead, the nation's largest reservoir, have drained at an alarming rate this year.
0000000029	In the US and Europe, ancient grains like protein-rich quinoa, farro and amaranth have been growing in popularity for the past decade and a half.
0000000030	Pair your cheese and charcuterie with a peachy drink. Peach lemonade can be served on its own or spiked with vodka or rum.
0000000031	In addition to enjoying them raw and cooked in desserts, fresh peaches can be roasted, pickled, and even frozen for a burst of summer sunshine in the middle of winter.
0000000032	These grains have remained largely unchanged over the past several hundred years, according to the Whole Grains Council.
0000000033	Less commonly known ancient grains include iron-rich teff, which has a distinctive nutty flavour but can be pricier than more common grains like oats. 
0000000034	Here's how you can maximize your peach perfection with recipe ideas for breakfast, lunch, dinner -- and dessert, of course.
0000000035	It's not all bad news, though, because the less secure teens "caught up" in their empathic behaviour by age 18, to Stern's surprise.
0000000036	Overnight oats are a trend that's not going away anytime soon, and summer is the ideal time to embrace this chilled-out breakfast dish. 
0000000037	This is cause for hope, she said, because it may indicate that those empathic skills can develop over time for adolescents who don't have great relationships at home. 
0000000038	You can experiment with these grains by incorporating them in small amounts into your morning bowl of oatmeal.
0000000039	This easily adaptable recipe can be made vegan with your choice of plant-based yogurt and milk, or with any combination of dairy that suits you.
0000000040	Add fresh sliced peaches to a mason jar with oats, milk and spices, and you've got a sweet peach cobbler-inspired treat waiting for you in the morning.
0000000041	Fire up the grill and give your peaches a little heat to turn them into a sweetly charred accompaniment for a number of dishes.
0000000042	It's hard to deny that tomatoes are the ideal summer food -- and that's saying a lot in a season where so much produce is at its peak. 
0000000043	But when a heat wave strikes, as one has throughout much of the United States over the past few weeks, the tomato really proves its worth.
0000000044	To grill peaches, preheat a gas or charcoal grill to medium heat. Halve and pit the peaches, then brush the cut halves with olive oil or vegetable oil.
0000000045	Though cooking tomatoes does boost their lycopene content, you'll still get enough from an uncooked tomato to make it worth your while, according to Manganiello. 
0000000046	If you really want to help up your antioxidant intake, add a little bit of olive oil.
0000000047	Place cut-side down and cook uncovered for 4 to 5 minutes, until grill marks appear and the peaches release easily from the grill grates.
0000000048	Stern suggested that having strong friendships or a trusted teacher might make an impact on insecure teens' empathy, but she said further research should be done to learn more.
0000000049	Grilled peaches become the star of the show in a big salad, like this quinoa, peach and summer vegetable salad that works as a main course. 
0000000050	Currently, all people arriving in the UK from a country on the government's amber list must quarantine for 10 days - regardless of whether they have had a coronavirus jab.
0000000051	"Consuming fresh tomatoes with a source of fat, such as olive oil, is a great way to boost lycopene absorption," she said.
0000000052	Southerners rave over the simplicity of a tomato sandwich on white bread, dressed lightly with mayonnaise and salt. 
0000000053	When it comes down to it, almost anything can be a salad or a sandwich -- the potential combinations are endless. 
0000000054	And if you want to pile on more ingredients, you'll find ways to make a tomato sandwich every day of the week.
0000000055	Swap out the mayonnaise for hummus, ranch dressing, cream cheese or spicy mustard. Add a sliced hard-boiled egg or avocado.
0000000056	Or simply drizzle them with balsamic vinegar and quality olive oil along with a sprinkling of flaky sea salt and serve as a fruit salad.
0000000057	Grab extra napkins for the juicy mess of cherry pepper relish or pickled onions. Or if you're in the mood for classic comfort, there's always the BLT.
0000000058	An outdoor happy hour is always happier with a special cocktail for sipping and a grazing board for snacking.
0000000059	Layer slices of fresh peaches or watermelon with tomatoes, mozzarella and basil on your salad platter, or for a kid-friendly twist, make caprese skewers.
0000000060	Turn it into the base for a Cobb salad with as many tomatoes and leftover fridge elements as you can handle. 
0000000061	Monday's results saw Ukraine and Finland finish third in their respective groups on three points apiece, meaning that if England did slip to that place they would still go through.
0000000062	Try this recipe as a start, and pick and choose add-ins like roasted red peppers and marinated chickpeas to suit your tastes.
0000000063	We all love slow-simmered marinara sauce for ladling over pasta, but the heat of July might not be the best time to cook up a big batch.
0000000064	Instead, stir up a no-cook tomato sauce that practically explodes with the juiciness of fresh tomatoes.
0000000065	The word "pesto" seems synonymous with basil, but tomatoes can find their way into this rustic sauce, too.
0000000066	Inappropriate laughter can sometimes be a sign that something is cognitively amiss. 
0000000067	He has again insisted that neither a lack of fitness nor speculation over his club future are the reasons for his lack of goals against Croatia and Scotland at Wembley.
0000000068	He has frequently insisted that neither a lack of fitness nor speculation over his club future are the reasons for his lack of goals against Croatia and Scotland at Wembley.
0000000069	Pickled peaches are a piquant complement to soft cheeses like fresh goat, Brie or Taleggio, which in turn taste fantastic with cured meats like prosciutto and speck.
0000000070	Either of these sauces also works well as a bruschetta and crostini topping for an impromptu happy hour with snacks.
0000000071	The results suggest that, in order to raise an empathic adolescent, parents need to model and encourage empathy.
0000000072	Since the research focused on averages across the study sample, she also said an examination of individual differences between participants is necessary.
0000000073	If you can't stand the heat, get out of the kitchen and fire up the grill.
0000000074	You won't have to spend much time over the flame, but if you want a hot meal on a hot day, grilled dishes with tomatoes fit the bill.
0000000075	Foil packet meals are quite possibly the easiest way to grill with very little mess and clean-up.
0000000076	Travelers in need of a digital detox, or just an escape from the stresses of recent times, will relish being marooned for a few days in this hard-to-reach tropical island.
0000000077	Place salmon fillets on a piece of heavy-duty foil drizzled with olive oil and load them up with halved cherry tomatoes and herbs like rosemary, dill or cilantro.
0000000078	This method is infinitely versatile -- so if you're craving other seafood, like shrimp or scallops, or more summer vegetables, you can customize it to each family member's tastes.
0000000079	Brian Cook, who had participated in the run and photographed the royal trio, sharing the snap on Twitter, said it was a "nice surprise, and nice of them to do".
0000000080	If chips and salsa are all you have an appetite for, make homemade salsa by charring whole tomatoes, peppers and onions on the grill. 
0000000081	For parents and even teachers, Stern advises understanding the necessity of empathy and really investing in relationships with teens. 
0000000082	A few minutes are enough to blister their skins and boost the flavour of the blend.
0000000083	Tomato water can be used in martinis and Bloody Marys or mixed with gin or vodka and tonic.
0000000084	This delicious salad is a meal to feel good about eating anytime and special enough for serving to guests too.
0000000085	Tomato water is nothing more than the slowly -- very slowly -- strained liquid from a tomato, and it's a low-maintenance way to make stellar drinks.
0000000086	Line a metal strainer with a flour sack towel or cheesecloth, then place it over a deep bowl.
0000000087	Chop tomatoes and sprinkle with salt, then pour into the towel and refrigerate for at least eight and up to 24 hours.
0000000088	There should be equipment stored close to the pool so that if someone begins drowning, it's at the ready for the person to grab on to for safety, she said.
0000000089	Prof Wren said it was "very encouraging" that more than 700,000 vaccine appointments were booked on the day that jabs became available to people aged 18 to 20 in England.
0000000090	We owe that notion to a comic-strip cartoonist named Elzie Crisler Segar, who created a character that he based on a rough-edged, hard-drinking local from his Illinois hometown.
0000000091	By 1933, when he began to appear as one of the lead characters in an animated cartoon series called "Thimble Theatre," Popeye was getting instant strength from spinach.
0000000092	These nitrates are rapidly depleted during exercise or physical exertion and replenishing them "increases force production in exercising skeletal muscle.
0000000093	"More research is being done now to determine if increased nitrate in muscle translates to increase muscle strength and improved athletic performance," Hord added.
0000000094	This jibes well with Hord's observation that spinach contains plenty of vitamin K, which helps lower blood pressure and the risk of cardiovascular disease.
0000000095	Unless it's cooked beyond recognition, spinach is also a good source of vitamin C. It has no cholesterol or fat.
0000000096	Harold McGee, the dean of culinary science, argued that there are better sources of strength-building minerals. 
0000000097	Though the iron of the pumping-iron set isn't what McGee means, it's iron that you want for sculpting bulging biceps and an admirable six-pack.
0000000098	Spinach has plenty of lutein, which is believed to support eye health and reduce the incidence of macular degeneration, a concern mostly of people 55 or older. 
0000000099	Leafy greens of many kinds, including cruciferous vegetables such as broccoli and bok choy, are known to inhibit heart disease and stroke, as well as certain cancers.
0000000100	Spinach joins these, with the greatest benefits derived from these vegetables in their raw or lightly cooked form.
0000000101	Finally, a diet that includes green leafy vegetables such as spinach, kale and greens, containing all the good things that Al Bochi noted, seems to help slow cognitive decline.
0000000102	Even with all its potential, Popeye's favourite food does have a few downsides. Spinach, especially raw spinach, can lend some people a, well, gassy air.
0000000103	"Too much of any food is not healthy," Hord said. "Spinach contains oxalic acid, which may bind minerals in the diet, like calcium, and render them unavailable for absorption."
0000000104	The tickets are paperless and passengers can use the updated season ticket calculator on the National Rail website to find out the best ticket for their route and travel patterns.
0000000105	If you're concerned about getting enough calcium in your system, it may be well to leave spinach out of the cheesy lasagnes in which it is so often deployed. 
0000000106	Too much oxalic acid is also a recipe for kidney stones, and therefore, Hord added, "this may negatively affect people" who are susceptible to them.
0000000107	All due respect to Popeye, a can may not be the tastiest way to introduce it to your table. 
0000000108	This is usually fine -- just remember that spinach can be a good vehicle for E. coli, Listeria and other harmful bacteria and germs.
0000000109	For this reason, the US Centres for Disease Control and Prevention recommends that spinach be cooked at 160º for 15 seconds, which kills potentially fatal bacteria.
0000000110	Lightly sautéing fresh spinach in a drizzle of olive or avocado oil meets this baseline, and it's tasty and nutritious as well.
0000000111	Another option is to wash spinach and other leafy greens thoroughly in running water before eating them.
0000000112	Adults should also encourage teens to invest in their relationships with their friends, which the study found helps build empathy as a skill as well, Stern said.
0000000113	Drinking up to three or four cups of caffeinated or decaffeinated coffee a day reduces your risk of developing and dying from chronic liver diseases, a new study found.
0000000114	"This would be especially valuable in countries with lower income and worse access to healthcare and where the burden of chronic liver disease is highest," Kennedy said.
0000000115	An early sign of dementia is an altered sense of humour and laughing at inappropriate moments, one study found.
0000000116	The rate of liver cancer has more than tripled between 1980 and today, "while the death rates have more than doubled," according to the American Cancer Society.
0000000117	Researchers followed a group of 9,000 children, who were taking part in a wider study, from the age of 7 to 24. 
0000000118	Food diaries were completed at age 7, 10 and 13, recording the food and drinks children consumed over three days.
0000000119	Measurements of body mass index, weight, waist circumference and body fat were also collected over the study period.
0000000120	The children were divided in five groups based on how much ultra-processed food they ate.
0000000121	In the lowest group, ultra-processed foods accounted for one fifth of their total diet, while in the highest group they accounted for more than two-thirds.
0000000122	However, she added, whom teenagers decide to befriend does matter.
0000000123	While the study shows a link between eating ultra processed foods and increases in BMI and body fat, it doesn't definitively show cause and effect.
0000000124	Previous studies on the same issue had yielded inconsistent findings but they involved fewer children and short follow-up periods, the researchers said.
0000000125	According to the researchers, more radical and effective measures are needed to reduce children's exposure and consumption of ultra-processed foods.
0000000126	For thousands of years, we've used one vegetable as a spice to flavour our toast, treat ear infections and ward off vampires: garlic.
0000000127	Garlic is the edible bulb of a plant in the lily family, native to central Asia.
0000000128	In addition to making food taste better, it has traditionally been used for health purposes by cultures such as the Egyptians, Greeks, Romans, Chinese and Japanese.
0000000129	The blood disorder porphyria may have supported this belief, according to the Carnegie Museum of Natural History. 
0000000130	A total of 7,723 new cases and 134 hospital admissions were found to have the Delta variant, which is thought to be about 60% more transmissible than the Alpha variant.
0000000131	It was found that while vaccines reduced the risk of being admitted to hospital, strong effects against the Delta variant were not seen until 28 days after the first jab.
0000000132	It's hard to separate the benefits of laughter and the context in which you would laugh.
0000000133	Allicin is also the compound to which most potential health benefits attributed to garlic have been credited. 
0000000134	Everyone likes a good belly laugh from time to time, and science supports that feeling.
0000000135	Studies have shown that laughing is linked to our physical, emotional and mental well-being -- even our relationships.
0000000136	Laughter is thought to have evolved as a form of social bonding in animals and as a way to express playful intention. 
0000000137	But humans don't need a physical trigger to laugh -- though generally we can't help but laugh if we're tickled.
0000000138	Janet Gibson, a professor emerita of cognitive psychology at Grinnell College in Iowa, said that laughter evolved in humans as a communication signal.
0000000139	A four-week-long study of employees of a car battery plant found that garlic reduced blood lead levels by 19%.
0000000140	Bundled garlic lies on display at the International Green Week agricultural trade fair in Berlin, Germany, on January 16, 2015.
0000000141	The idea was that laughter was an external signal that can tell the group everything is OK, we can relax.
0000000142	Additionally, many of these studies have used garlic that is a very high dose, concentrated or given in a form of stabilized allicin.
0000000143	The connection between sleep, dementia and early death from any cause is especially worrisome, experts say, due to the poor sleep habits of Americans and people all around the world.
0000000144	And the belief is, is that over the centuries, the brain kept these connections so that we now laugh when ... we hear things that are relaxing, funny, surprising, amusing.
0000000145	Mr. Bezos is set to beat his rival Richard Branson and his space enterprise Virgin Galactic in being the very first person to make space travel available to the public.
0000000146	Given these issues, you might think that people could just eat raw garlic for health benefits.
0000000147	Anthropologists think that laughter is universal, but that doesn't mean every culture finds the same things funny.
0000000148	An entire week of disrupted sleep increased the amount of tau, another protein responsible for the tangles associated with Alzheimer's, frontal lobe dementia and Lewy body disease, the study found.
0000000149	Laughter is a surprisingly complicated process, engaging multiple regions of the brain and the body.
0000000150	The frontal lobe is thought to help you interpret the various bits of information you receive -- the sounds and images -- and then it decides whether they are funny. 
0000000151	City fought from behind but were denied their first home win over Fulham for 28 years.
0000000152	This simultaneous Home Movies posting is at an end.
0000000153	The Spanish side are the top scorers in this season’s competition with 18 goals.
0000000154	Hopefully the 2 new signing can get some game time also.
0000000155	Gazza, 50, is said to have given a heartfelt eulogy to his dad.
0000000156	He is 34 and married with two children.
0000000157	Milburn and Reverend and the Makers play Bearded Theory festival, 24-27 May.
0000000158	More than 20,000 pills were found and over a dozen different types of drug.
0000000159	Electronic control via 12-pin broadcast connector.
0000000160	This place knows how to throw a party.
0000000161	This new exhibition has roamed the continent to bring these works back to Britain.
0000000162	According to BBC 6 Music it is “the Shoreditch of the north”.
0000000163	This requires 308 votes as it would require an amendment to the constitution.
0000000164	Prosser’s conversion made it 14-5.
0000000165	Prior to that they had succumbed 3-2 at home to Salford City.
0000000166	The account had raised £140 before it was reported to police.
0000000167	Roads have been closed on the South Island following the storm.
0000000168	The Dow suffered its worst percentage drop since June 2016.
0000000169	Crystal Palace haven’t won in the league without Zaha since September 2016.
0000000170	The 47-year-old breached a restraining order by writing to the BBC journalist.
0000000171	UG News editor since early 2013.
0000000172	Here's a roundup on 10 popular destinations that are open. 
0000000173	A year ago, Sunderland came to south London and won 4-0.
0000000174	Rangers enjoyed a superb Saturday afternoon.
0000000175	True, the trees will someday grow back, John admits.
0000000176	The series ran for seven reasons.
0000000177	Emergency services were originally called at 11.
0000000178	He had held the position since 2010.
0000000179	He has been very disappointing for the last 18 months.
0000000180	Mining had originally been expected to begin in 2012.
0000000181	He now claims to have 161.
0000000182	The trailer for the new series dropped yesterday.
0000000183	Big turnovers by Stewart, who threw three interceptions, helped Denver.
0000000184	The family moved to mainland Britain in 1919.
0000000185	These are external links and will open in a new window.
0000000186	Chris has been a journalist since the 1990s.
0000000187	This was matched by a dive downward by bassoons, bass clarinet, trombones and bass tuba.
0000000188	Parties finally make their appearance on page 177.
0000000189	As I write, it’s June 2017.
0000000190	This year Presidents’ Day falls on February 19.
0000000191	As evening approaches, tennis, volleyball, and softball get going.
0000000192	Gillette was shot to death Friday at an eighth grade graduation dance he organized.
0000000193	Boxing News went to visit the Eubanks at the gym in Hove.
0000000194	This after Forbes reported that he made 12 million.
0000000195	While annoying, slamming seems to happen to very few consumers.
0000000196	But the 21st-century Commonwealth can do better.
0000000197	The winery's diaphanous stone facade links it to the architects' European work.
0000000198	The 36-year-old remains as committed to tennis as ever.
0000000199	The STR13 appears to feature a similar livery compared with its predecessor.
0000000200	Elizabeth Robinson was 76 at the time.
0000000201	I've been to over 50 countries.
0000000202	The 36-year-old has enjoyed a stunning 13 months.
0000000203	That N70 million was money gathered from the 7th Senate.
0000000204	It was much more about zero waste and being sustainable.
0000000205	This is, however, accompanied by a lack of fast twitch fibbers.
0000000206	His new role has become effective as of 8 January 2018.
0000000207	This can give you a pain-killing sensation.
0000000208	The eagle hatched at a nest site in the Borders in 2017.
0000000209	The couple's dream of staying in the Northwest was uprooted.
0000000210	After the crash, their relationship became known.
0000000211	Burnley is 45 minutes up the road.
0000000212	Catch EastEnders tonight at 8pm on BBC One.
0000000213	However, KGB Cleaning reneged on this in March 2017.
0000000214	Formula 1 car launches are always steeped in optimism.
0000000215	Now, child protection and LAC dominate with over 70% of total spend.
0000000216	It’s 9pm at Mr. Chow in Knightsbridge, and things are getting serious.
0000000217	Like the western zodiac, it is divided into 12 sections.
0000000218	They removed the CD drives.
0000000219	The 2013 final was brought up.
0000000220	Chiltern Railways say they are running an amended timetable.
0000000221	ISAs contributed to 15% of 2017 net sales.
0000000222	Melisa says wherever that place may be, it won't be in a large city.
0000000223	They struck the winner 65 minutes into the game at Portman Road.
0000000224	The run doesn’t encompass only the 4-1 defeat to Cardiff.
0000000225	The arrests and broadcast bans have shocked many Kenyans.
0000000226	Next year’s Show will be held in Atlanta from January 14-16, 2019.
0000000227	For reference, 1 Fluid Ounce is 986 standard Drops.
0000000228	We had compulsory attendance at Episcopal chapel services eight times a week.
0000000229	The Air went on sale in Korea in March 2016.
0000000230	The pair had dipped as low as 10%.
0000000231	The Swiss Franc, Australian and New Zealand dollars also saw significant losses.
0000000232	Iceland has a small population, of around 340,000 people.
0000000233	His last start came in the win over Harlequins on December 10.
0000000234	The 25-year-old underwent knee surgery over the weekend.
0000000235	Hard Sun airs tonight at 9:30PM on BBC One.
0000000236	Up to 200 employees may be affected by this announcement.
0000000237	This game was not going to be like that.
0000000238	Charter flights are offered in summer from 25 UK airports.
0000000239	LOVE Somebody follows the duo’s 2016 smash Capsize and versatile EP Truce.
0000000240	This is a state which is 1,100 years old.
0000000241	Economists forecast the index will have climbed from 55.
0000000242	A DB cash balance scheme will sit alongside it.
0000000243	HARRY Arter insists he is “100 per cent committed” to Cherries.
0000000244	But the zoo is continuing to roll out shots to protect other animals.
0000000245	It now threatens to sink the 52-year-old and his estimated £470m fortune.
0000000246	Head to the Suzuki Main Stage at 12.
0000000247	He could have gifted the hosts a goal early on.
0000000248	The 100 had such a nice time.
0000000249	Nicola Sturgeon has just tweeted about the situation on the M80.
0000000250	Each has outpaced the Thomson Reuters Same Store Sales Index.
0000000251	Arsenal have been a bit inconsistent.
0000000252	The taxi was returned to its owner at 8am.
0000000253	The Brighton man dished out some punishment in a segment for talkSPORT.
0000000254	It wasn’t good, but you could turn that around in 24 hours.
0000000255	She is 31 weeks pregnant.
0000000256	A provisional patent was filed for the technology in December 2017.
0000000257	The winner advances to the April 21-22 semi-finals.
0000000258	Seasoning is salt, pepper and perhaps cayenne.
0000000259	Readership declines through the week and is lowest on the weekends.
0000000260	France host Italy in the Six Nations 2018 this evening.
0000000261	106 nursery workers would lose their jobs.
0000000262	The Belgium international has been in talks over a new deal.
0000000263	This was in 1951, when the company started manufacturing in Mumbai.
0000000264	So far only 35 replacement properties have been finished.
0000000265	I teach some courses to adult learners.
0000000266	The company made more than £100m in profit last year.
0000000267	You'd be surprised at just how outrageous or outlandish some of the claims are.
0000000268	The show ran from 1998 to 2004, and spawned two movies.
0000000269	The T3 has 6 anchor points tested to EN795.
0000000270	EPIC acquired St Paul’s House in March 2016 with 30% office vacancy.
0000000271	The former Chase chairman had given away about 900 million before he died.
0000000272	The week in markets commencing 5 February 2018 fits the bill.
0000000273	It's just a tool in your medicine cabinet to help you feel better.
0000000274	The Magpies were doing all of the early probing.
0000000275	The new Fortnite Season Battle Pass will be arriving on February 21st.
0000000276	Only about 200 verified Martian meteorites have been found on Earth.
0000000277	That’s been 30 years of happiness.
0000000278	Showers likely, mainly after 4am.
0000000279	Donny George died of a heart attack in 2011, aged only 60.
0000000280	The New England Patriots were beaten 41-33 by the Philadelphia Eagles.
0000000281	Maybe in China they know something we don’t.
0000000282	The group has been helmed by four generations of the Burgess family.
0000000283	There’s something profoundly nourishing about it, especially for £8.
0000000284	Officers from British Transport Police were called at 11.
0000000285	The second leg takes place at Old Trafford on March 13.
0000000286	The film is scheduled for a March 29th 2018 release.
0000000287	The final decision will be taken on February 15.
0000000288	On Friday, the Dow Jones fell 665.
0000000289	Mary Magdalene is released in cinemas nationwide on 16th March.
0000000290	Dividend payments to shareholders grew to £68 billion in 2017.
0000000291	Articles dealing with kidney and diuretics and dopamine were searched.
0000000292	He was voted Columnist of the Year 2015.
0000000293	By the late eighties, it was healthier food, with less fat and cholesterol.
0000000294	My 10-year old Labrador has developed a new habit.
0000000295	Cookies are a firm favourite.
0000000296	If he reaches 360 innings it becomes a player option.
0000000297	It's very hard to explain why something is funny.
0000000298	But sometimes sounds or words can just be inherently funny.
0000000299	There are beautiful vistas, secluded villages, and a range of exhilarating walks en route.
0000000300	Laughter can also have a dark side.
0100000001	Why not make a different point?
0100000002	Who will suffer if it goes wrong?
0100000003	What is wrong in shaking hands with someone for courtesy sake?
0100000004	How much money does the UK make every 60 seconds?
0100000005	Who was the president at that time?
0100000006	How can I survive somewhere where I have no one?
0100000007	You've never seen a white board used in real technical development, have you?
0100000008	What can the special counsel investigate?
0100000009	How do you feel Young Farmers has impacted your life?
0100000010	And how long will he be allowed to go on?
0100000011	How has demand for home loans been in this year so far?
0100000012	When does the meeting start?
0100000013	Where do you stand on this issue?
0100000014	The question is what are you going to do about it?
0100000015	Scientifically speaking, what is the purpose of laughter?
0100000016	What might you be worrying about?
0100000017	How much longer should I expect to wait?
0100000018	Can you come back tomorrow?
0100000019	Why would I just walk away and be left jobless?
0100000020	What just happened to our system?
0100000021	If someone were to say, whose is that?
0100000022	How should a prospect move regarding this?
0100000023	What happened to winning at all costs?
0100000024	How many engine parts has Ricciardo already used?
0100000025	Is his attitude good or not good?
0100000026	What do you mean by this?
0100000027	Even if you cancel it, how does it help the country?
0100000028	Would you like a cup of tea?
0100000029	What about all my male friends?
0100000030	What can I say about his motivation?
0100000031	What’s the best way to improve communication between healthcare professionals and patients?
0100000032	But what about the protocols that govern those interactions?
0100000033	Was that what you were talking about?
0100000034	Have you purchased a home abroad?
0100000035	Did you catch my drift?
0100000036	And who can ask for more than that in life?
0100000037	If not, what is the alternative?
0100000038	Prior to Love Island, what was your biggest claim to fame?
0100000039	Once the trash reaches the ocean, where does it all go?
0100000040	Why were no proactive measures being taken on this matter?
0100000041	So what are we missing today?
0100000042	What was your biggest break this year?
0100000043	How can banks convince depositors that their money is safe?
0100000044	What is Queen Elizabeth II’s net worth?
0100000045	Is that your final decision?
0100000046	Did you tell them where we'd be?
0100000047	Could this be the key to a longer life?
0100000048	Could this be Pat Phelan playing fresh mind games with his prey?
0100000049	Have you noticed this awareness influence the conversation about women in literature?
0100000050	Are you the one looking after your kid later?
0100000051	Is it affordable for smaller businesses?
0100000052	Can’t a woman lunge in peace while taking a call?
0100000053	Did anybody really think he would still be here by now?
0100000054	Does meditation result in new neurons, actually changing brain structure?
0100000055	When did you arrive last night?
0100000056	Have you been a prudent investor these last two years?
0100000057	Or did they come in by some other route?
0100000058	Is there any mention of prophetesses in the chapter just read?
0100000059	Have you got personal experience of it?
0100000060	Where shall we have lunch?
0100000061	Do they maintain those behavioural standards at home, in wider society?
0100000062	Did they really sail on Tuesday?
0100000063	Do you have any dashcam clips you would like to share?
0100000064	Are you excited for May 24th?
0100000065	Shall I forgive my brother seven times?
0100000066	Has anyone ever used acupuncture or hypnosis as a form of pain management?
0100000067	Are you a parent with an adult child still living at home?
0100000068	Am I charged for the items as soon as I order them?
0100000069	Does your business need employees with these qualities?
0100000070	I don’t know what happened, did he not touch the ball well?
0100000071	How can we get in touch?
0100000072	How long have you been living there?
0100000073	Why do you think that?
0100000074	Is she now simply whacking clients, having relieved them of their cash?
0100000075	It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
0100000076	Is it as drastic as it sounds?
0100000077	Can we start with the jobless figures?
0100000078	How can I help you?
0100000079	How long have you been waiting?
0100000080	But is Clara just a pawn in a much larger game?
0100000081	Can you tell me about your testing process?
0100000082	Am I again trying to dominate a conversation?
0100000083	Do I need my neighbours' approval to have it fixed?
0100000084	Can we close that gap in one season?
0100000085	Does this mean we should ignore what people tell us in research?
0100000086	Can you say how the two things are linked?
0100000087	The place is beautiful, isn't it?
0100000088	Could broadcasting afford not to follow suit?
0100000089	Or do you actually want to change behaviours and beliefs?
0100000090	Is it to confuse society and justify his own stand?
0100000091	What kind of unforeseen adventures has it sparked?
0100000092	But will they believe his lies as he tries to evade punishment?
0100000093	Can you explain a bit more about that?
0100000094	Is he a good person or a bad person?
0100000095	Can I withdraw my application after I have submitted it?
0100000096	Is this our course of action today?
0100000097	But thanks so much to the backstage crew and production guys!
0100000098	How much do I need to sleep?
0100000099	Just bring a lively mind and lots of enthusiasm!
0100000100	But the festivities don’t stop there!
0200000001	I'm done playing games with you!
0200000002	Do it again, if you dare!
0200000003	I knew I shouldn't have come along!
0200000004	I knew you could do it!
0200000005	Crickey that was one tense episode for them!
0200000006	Just wanted to confirm it’s not a thing!
0200000007	That’s a good one for you!
0200000008	He reminded me of that when he joined!
0200000009	I've have such a long day!
0200000010	Men come in all shapes, sizes, colours and creeds!
0200000011	The Awards will be in Los Angeles and it will be fun!
0200000012	I often wish she could talk and wonder what she would say!
0200000013	I want to have that outfit!
0200000014	But that didn’t seem to stop the speculation!
0200000015	It was a bit telling about the level of fighting!
0200000016	Eye on the prize at all times!
0200000017	It doesn’t get any better than that!
0200000018	I’ve told him it is supposed to be coming!
0200000019	It’s time for a break!
0200000020	Congratulations to our 2018 Top Employers!
0200000021	Congrats, you won first place!
0200000022	That doesn’t happen to me!
0200000023	Because they didn’t want to, and now they just talk!
0200000024	You should really mind your own business!
0200000025	Last but not least, the staff was amazing, very friendly and helpful!
0200000026	But we’ll work with anyone!
0200000027	And drinking lots and lots of water!
0200000028	She preferred it quiet, and me, not so much!
0200000029	I can't believe you didn't tell me earlier!
0200000030	But we know what you really want!
0200000031	I nearly fell off the bus!
0200000032	I want to thank you for a good job!
0200000033	That kills the second shooter angle of this!
0200000034	Home is where the heart is, and the heart is feeling good!
0200000035	Same negative stories over and over again!
0200000036	I feel like one of the old guys here now!
0200000037	I’ve never felt love and happiness like this I could burst!
0200000038	That is not going to happen!
0200000039	But of course, in this scenario, it’s not even relevant!
0200000040	No one was interested in us at all!
0200000041	I’ll keep you posted and thanks for cheering me on!
0200000042	It was the greatest feeling ever!
0200000043	I want to talk to your manager, now!
0200000044	Click this link and enter your details!
0200000045	And he looked exactly the same!
0200000046	That player would be worth £400m!
0200000047	I mean, come on, you never do that to pizza!
0200000048	I do not think there is more coercion and pain!
0200000049	I want to know what they have to say!
0200000050	I dare you to do that again!
0200000051	But if she doesn’t bind it off correctly at the end—whoosh!
0200000052	But don’t forget about the opposing team!
0200000053	Watch out, the floor is very slippery!
0200000054	Get back to the basics and make us all proud!
0200000055	And they do deliveries too!
0200000056	And then you lift those!
0200000057	How's that for a taste of your own medicine!
0200000058	So amazing to have my parents out here supporting as well!
0200000059	So that’s it for the singing, and the voting is open!
0200000060	We need to evacuate pronto!
0200000061	That was the most delicious meal I've ever had!
0200000062	And not to forget the magic seeds!
0200000063	I am so proud of you!
0200000064	You won't believe what just happened!
0200000065	I could play better than that!
0200000066	I was looking to try and get the assist!
0200000067	Now that would be something!
0200000068	I have no time to have a writer's block!
0200000069	Both Geo and Alana are doing great!
0200000070	It smells like burnt bacon in here!
0200000071	Just fill in the form below!
0200000072	Must always report such instances to authorities, again and again!
0200000073	Get out there and make your mark upon the world, adventurer!
0200000074	Thank you for being there even in the hardest of times!
0200000075	It could get funky in the jungle!
0200000076	One of them is leaving over that bridge!
0200000077	I was not good enough!
0200000078	You are only 30 minutes late!
0200000079	It’s the match Twitter’s been waiting for!
0200000080	Just tune in daily and participate!
0200000081	He just had to score!
0200000082	A day to celebrate and lift each other up!
0200000083	A rapid start and it got even better for him!
0200000084	That was the worst idea I've ever heard!
0200000085	Only a child would believe that story!
0200000086	All that and more on today’s rundown!
0200000087	And every year it gets that little bit harder!
0200000088	And for £5, you can easily do the same at home!
0200000089	And join us next Wednesday for another F1 Report!
0200000090	And not just in Geri’s front room!
0200000091	And now he’s done the simple stuff in a simple manner!
0200000092	And of course we can do this!
0200000093	And old enough to buy his mum a beer!
0200000094	And the truth will set you free!
0200000095	And then one day we just kissed, and that was that!
0200000096	And then we know we’re in trouble, one or the other!
0200000097	And you know what, we lived to tell the tale!
0200000098	Anything that doesn’t involve you using much energy!
0200000099	Be a Warrior and get yours now!
0200000100	Because I have a list of both!
0300000001	I D K what you mean. 
0300000002	I think the service was good but Y M M V.
0300000003	The song W A P was a certified hit.
0300000004	I usually wear size X L.
0300000005	I'm going to close the account I have with H S B C.
0300000006	I'm thinking about getting a Toyota Camry L X.
0300000007	He went to the store to get some O T C cold medication.
0300000008	He rapped about cars and was especially fond of the Dodge S R T.
0300000009	They hired a P R firm for the event.
0300000010	Turn up the A C please.
0300000011	What are the X P rates in game?
0300000012	He gave me a bottle of X O cognac as a gift.
0300000013	Should I use the S K S?
0300000014	My name is spelled S Y D.
0300000015	I mean wood, W O O D not would.
0300000016	He rushed and joined the D T D fraternity.
0300000017	I usually play it on my P C.
0300000018	You should get an S T D test immediately.
0300000019	I'm getting closer, E T A 20 minutes.
0300000020	The goods had to pass through the H M R C.
0300000021	He was stopped by the N Y P D.
0300000022	The zipper was stamped with the letters Y K K.
0300000023	I want to exchange G B P for U S D.
0300000024	You must check in with a P O as per terms of your probation.
0300000025	Have you decided between taking A P and I B classes?
0300000026	D I Y crafts has become popular in recent years.
0300000027	It requires O E M parts.
0300000028	The show starts at five o'clock G M T.
0300000029	Please stay around after the show for an F A Q.
0300000030	I'm on my way, I'll be there A S A P.
0300000031	Good luck on the I G C S E tomorrow!
0300000032	He was on the cover of X X L magazine.
0300000033	Let's go to the pub and grab an I P A after work.
0300000034	I'm going to go grab a snack, B R B.
0300000035	I bought the U K version of the console. 
0300000036	Please send in your C V before Monday for consideration for the position.
0300000037	You will need your I D when checking in.
0300000038	I heard F T made a report on the subject.
0300000039	Please R S V P if you are going to my party.
0300000040	The C P I tracks inflation.
0300000041	You need a J D degree to practice law.
0300000042	He received his disability payments from the D L A every month.
0300000043	The soldier was declared M I A and is presumed dead.
0300000044	There's nothing to watch on I T V at this time.
0300000045	The voters overwhelmingly supported the B N P.
0300000046	I need to hire a D J for my wedding party.
0300000047	Have you taken your F C E exams yet?
0300000048	I do have some O C D tendencies.
0300000049	He was accepted into L S E to study political science.
0300000050	I usually support Liverpool F C.