4000000001	We also have them in a larger size if those don't fit.
4000000002	Unfortunately, the warehouse is out of stock.
4000000003	Would you prefer red or brown?
4000000004	What kind of shoes are you looking for?
4000000005	Have you ever heard of Oxford shoes? We have a pair of that kind.
4000000006	Is this for you or for someone else?
4000000007	Have a seat and try them on.
4000000008	Let me know if you need anything else.
4000000009	How is the fit for that pair?
4000000010	We also have that dress in a smaller size.
4000000011	Let me check our website to see if we have that model.
4000000012	This one is really nice, it was made in Italy.
4000000013	Feel the material, it's very soft.
4000000014	The fitting rooms are just at the back of the store.
4000000015	Call me if you need me to bring over something else.
4000000016	Would you like that wrapped up?
4000000017	Will you be picking up in-store or shall we ship it to you?
4000000018	I'll just staple the receipt to the bag.
4000000019	Thank you for shopping with us!
4000000020	If you're gaming, you'll definitely need a better GPU.
4000000021	This is a six-core CPU, so it's great for video editing.
4000000022	Will you also need to purchase a monitor?
4000000023	We have a monitors of all sizes.
4000000024	Have you considered upgrading to an SSD?
4000000025	If you're just doing casual gaming, package A will be more than enough.
4000000026	For an extra twenty pounds, we can add on another three years of warranty.
4000000027	This is the newest model that just came out last week.
4000000028	We recommend future-proofing, but some people aren't into that.
4000000029	Great, we'll send your new computer out immediately.
4000000030	All the fruits and vegetables in this section are organic.
4000000031	We imported this beef from New Zealand and it's one hundred percent hormone-free.
4000000032	The food we prepare here is all made with non-GMO ingredients.
4000000033	We can also deliver that to you if you'd prefer.
4000000034	You can find that in the deli section.
4000000035	Looks like we're all sold out, but let me just check the back.
4000000036	Fresh salmon is on special for today only.
4000000037	We should be getting more strawberries in the next few days.
4000000038	Last time I checked, we only had that brand.
4000000039	Okay, I will let the manager know.
4000000040	We sell new and used cars, and sometimes motorcycles, too.
4000000041	Have you thought about going with an all-electric vehicle?
4000000042	I would personally not recommend that model, it has quite a bit of issues.
4000000043	It is a Korean company, and they've been making cars for years.
4000000044	Let's take it out for a ride so you can see for yourself.
4000000045	A five-year warranty is included on all twenty  models.
4000000046	The main difference is the leather interior.
4000000047	If you ask me, I'd definitely get the premium upgrade.
4000000048	All our used vehicles are over on the right side.
4000000049	We can also lease any of the cars you see here.
4000000050	The nice thing about this one is that it is a convertible.
4000000051	If you buy now, you pay no interest for the next year.
4000000052	These jams are all locally-made, so the taste is very fresh.
4000000053	For this weekend only, if you buy two, you get one free.
4000000054	Have you shopped with us before?
4000000055	We charge for bags, so customers usually bring their own.
4000000056	Would you like an electronic copy of your receipt?
4000000057	You can find more of our products in our online store.
4000000058	The price is slightly better if you buy in-store.
4000000059	The product you are asking about is only sold online.
4000000060	Let me try and look up the model number.
4000000061	Bundles are always cheaper and include more products.
4000000062	That console is a limited edition, so we won't be getting any more stock.
4000000063	You can pay in instalments for six or twelve months.
4000000064	The price already includes tax.
4000000065	If this is a gift for someone, I can wrap it up for you.
4000000066	Are you paying with credit or debit?
4000000067	Sorry, we only take cash.
4000000068	No returns are allowed on personal goods.
4000000069	Make sure to keep it in the fridge and it will last a while.
4000000070	We can throw in a few accessories for free.
4000000071	This is our best-seller, and we sell a lot of it.
4000000072	It comes in black or white.
4000000073	What size do you normally wear?
4000000074	Try on these two and see which fits better.
4000000075	You said you have a coupon for this?
4000000076	Have you taken any courses with us before?
4000000077	We offer certificate and diploma programmes.
4000000078	It usually takes four years to complete, but some people do it in less.
4000000079	We have many options for people who wish to study part-time.
4000000080	You can check the website to see what scholarships we offer.
4000000081	Most of the scholarships are merit-based.
4000000082	We have two campuses, which one were you thinking of?
4000000083	We are currently not accepting applications for that course.
4000000084	What kind of area of study would you like to go into?
4000000085	Transport around the campus is very convenient.
4000000086	We have two restaurants, a pub, and a Starbucks.
4000000087	That course is only offered during the day-time.
4000000088	Have you checked out our night school programmes?
4000000089	You can choose between the HTML or the Python course.
4000000090	Once you complete the programme, you'll receive a certificate.
4000000091	How experienced with computers would you say you are?
4000000092	We have something for students of all levels.
4000000093	Classes are forty five minutes with fifteen-minute breaks in between.
4000000094	We usually suggest taking two classes every week, but you can do more, too.
4000000095	Our instructors have all studied at the conservatory of music.
4000000096	We offer group lessons and private lessons.
4000000097	You can take a free thirty-minute class to see if you like it.
4000000098	A live performance is one of the requirements for receiving the certificate.
4000000099	There are also some intensive courses you can take on weekends.
4000000100	We don't offer scholarships, but students do get ten percent off.
4000000101	We divide our classes by age and language level.
4000000102	Teachers in the advanced courses won't let students speak in their mother tongue.
4000000103	You can speak another language other than English in the English-only zone over there.
4000000104	Most of our students are from Asia, but we also have some from Europe.
4000000105	Because of the current global situation, we only have online courses.
4000000106	The school organises activities every weekend that help students practise what they've learnt.
4000000107	You could also hire a tutor since it's usually more inexpensive.
4000000108	Textbooks are not included, and they are not optional.
4000000109	Let me show you around the building.
4000000110	There usually is quite a bit of homework, so the course isn't for everyone.
4000000111	The English linguistics course is only for advanced learners.
4000000112	Most courses are in the morning.
4000000113	Classes are from eight to eleven every morning.
4000000114	We have been around for over thirty years.
4000000115	Our boxing class is the most popular.
4000000116	We are currently all booked out for the morning slot on Saturday.
4000000117	You can bring your own equipment, or you can use what we have available.
4000000118	Safety equipment is mandatory for everyone.
4000000119	We don't have any karate lessons.
4000000120	We can set you up with a private instructor if you'd like.
4000000121	We have a school tournament for students every six months.
4000000122	Classes for children are the same price as adult classes.
4000000123	You are welcome to take a look.
4000000124	Our main coach is in a class, but he'll be out soon.
4000000125	I can get someone else to show you around.
4000000126	Your product is still under warranty.
4000000127	Just send it back to us and we'll take care of it.
4000000128	Would you like me to help you troubleshoot over the phone?
4000000129	You can contact us seven days a week.
4000000130	Is it OK if I put you on hold for a minute?
4000000131	At which location did you purchase the product?
4000000132	What seems to be the problem with your TV?
4000000133	Looks like the warranty expired a few weeks ago.
4000000134	Did you purchase extended warranty?
4000000135	Our warranty only covers parts, not labour.
4000000136	Was it previously fixed by one of our qualified technicians?
4000000137	We offer a money-back guarantee for thirty days.
4000000138	We can send you a replacement or refund your money.
4000000139	That is not a defect, it is actually a feature.
4000000140	You can disable that function if it bothers you.
4000000141	It seems your laptop isn't compatible with the dock.
4000000142	We can upgrade some components for free.
4000000143	Shipping is not covered under warranty.
4000000144	I'll send you a link to a list of all the compatible accessories.
4000000145	Let me just confirm your address.
4000000146	It usually takes a few days to fix and no more than a week.
4000000147	All of our employees have been trained properly.
4000000148	You have to make an appointment if you're bringing your car in.
4000000149	While it's being repaired, you can rent one of our cars.
4000000150	If you want to avoid waiting, our online support is always faster.
4000000151	We just need to verify your information first.
4000000152	Since it is an old model, we can replace it with a newer version.
4000000153	All returns require a receipt.
4000000154	We recommend bringing it in every three years for maintenance.
4000000155	We can also take care of assembly for an extra fifty five pounds.
4000000156	If you encounter any problems, feel free to give us a call.
4000000157	Installation can be complicated, but we have technicians who can do it for you.
4000000158	We are calling to inform you there's a recall for a product you purchased.
4000000159	That feature is sold as an add-on, it isn't included.
4000000160	I'm sorry to hear that, we'll send you a replacement right away.
4000000161	You should charge your laptop for twenty four hours the first time.
4000000162	Batteries only last a few years, so it sounds like yours needs replacing.
4000000163	I'm calling to let you know your order has been delayed.
4000000164	Is the address we have on file correct?
4000000165	If your computer is overheating, you may want to think about water cooling.
4000000166	Your warranty is almost over.
4000000167	A year of cloud storage is included with your subscription.
4000000168	We only sell that product to customers who have the proper certificate.
4000000169	We can provide on-site training.
4000000170	If you'd like to learn more about your new product, give us a call!
4000000171	We ship world-wide, but shipping time is a few weeks.
4000000172	Overheating is a common problem for that model, and it is covered under warranty.
4000000173	Please take it to one of our service centres to get it repaired.
4000000174	I am not able to provide that kind of information over the phone.
4000000175	We'd just like to ask you a few questions about your product.
4000000176	Would you be willing to participate in a quick survey about your purchase?
4000000177	Enter that code on our website to receive an extra fifteen percent off.
4000000178	Do you have a points card?
4000000179	Hello, we're just calling to make sure your appliances are working properly.
4000000180	We'll send you a replacement if our technician isn't able to fix the problem.
4000000181	We can provide training for an additional one hundred and fifty pounds.
4000000182	For assistance with installation, please call or visit our website.
4000000183	You can receive another fifteen percent discount if you sign up for our newsletter.
4000000184	Would you like to join our loyalty programme?
4000000185	Achieve commercial excellence through pricing optimisation and sales execution.
4000000186	We help clients improve efficiency and innovate for the future.
4000000187	The length of a project depends on various factors, like budget and organisation size.
4000000188	Each project is designed to meet the specific needs of our clients.
4000000189	We have over twenty years providing business solutions.
4000000190	We focus on the success of our clients.
4000000191	We use cookies to improve your experience.
4000000192	The scope is determined mainly based on the business goals and challenges.
4000000193	We typically recommend an assessment phase at the beginning of each project.
4000000194	Our solutions are flexible and meant to solve countless challenges.
4000000195	We eliminate travel as much as possible to save time and money.
4000000196	The proposal will include a statement and scope of work, pricing, timelines, and recommendations.
4000000197	Volume discounts range anywhere from ten to thirty percent of our typical consulting rates.
4000000198	The design phase is used to design a training program from start to finish.
4000000199	Business process mapping is essential to business process improvement.
4000000200	Operational redundancy reduces risk in the event that key talent leaves or is unavailable.
4000000201	Business process improvement can only be done with accurate process documentation.
4000000202	Acquisition requirements often include detailed process documentation.
4000000203	Your organisational strategy is critical for defining how your business will operate.
4000000204	We can develop, distribute, and provide comprehensive reporting for any type of employee survey.
4000000205	You can't move the date up.
4000000206	A small Run Box will pop up.
4000000207	Basically they will sync up like this.
4000000208	Can you please spell your first name?
4000000209	I wasn't quite able to hear that.
4000000210	OK, and your password is case sensitive.
4000000211	OK, I will need that code, please.
4000000212	Please check if the internet is working.
4000000213	Right, is there an icon for it?
4000000214	So it has a black screen?
4000000215	Sorry, you want to change what exactly?
4000000216	The small button below the Xbox button.
4000000217	There's nothing that can be done, sir.
4000000218	Who does the Xbox profile belong to?
4000000219	Yeah, you got the ten percent discount.
4000000220	You have access to your Xbox account.
4000000221	I will guide you to get the installation.
4000000222	I'll be back with you in a moment.
4000000223	Is it asking you for the product key?
4000000224	Keep the following product ID in your records.
4000000225	Let me quickly validate it on my end.
4000000226	No, there's no way we can do that.
4000000227	Now, click on "next" to activate your software.
4000000228	Oh, let’s see on which account was that.
4000000229	OK, so I want you to sign in.
4000000230	Please read it to me, I'll check it.
4000000231	Press the power button to boot it up.
4000000232	Send the verification codes to the email address.
4000000233	Sir, could you please reconfirm the eighth group?
4000000234	So I just went through your order number.
4000000235	So is it Microsoft Windows or Microsoft Office?
4000000236	Is your computer connected to the internet?
4000000237	That is going to cost about forty pounds.
4000000238	The email for the Xbox, what it is?
4000000239	There're no bank cards on this Microsoft account.
4000000240	This escalation was not approved by this team.
4000000241	This is all the information I have, sorry.
4000000242	This is what they can do for you.
4000000243	Twenty three pounds and ninety seven pence, yes.
4000000244	Was your product linked with your Microsoft account?
4000000245	We would have to do an escalation form.
4000000246	What do mean, sorry, can you just explain?
4000000247	Yeah, let's go with your email address.
4000000248	Yes, I'm still here, sir, on the line.
4000000249	Yes, that could be one of the reasons.
4000000250	Yes, you can use this product key, sir.
4000000251	You network is not appropriate for your headset.
4000000252	Alright, is it a new copy or an upgrade?
4000000253	Alright, no sound on the on the headset, alright.
4000000254	And is this the first time you're contacting Microsoft?
4000000255	But I've got to check for the email address.
4000000256	Give it a moment and it should come back.
4000000257	I think that we've got a big problem here.
4000000258	I'm here, do you have the verification code?
4000000259	Is your son logged into the Xbox right now?
4000000260	It was originally a free upgrade from Windows seven.
4000000261	OK, do you have the installation ID with you?
4000000262	Can you see something on the screen?
4000000263	You're just going to receive a verification code.
4000000264	Once again, we cannot provide you with another extension.
4000000265	Renew the subscription, or it will go into reduced functionality.
4000000266	Sir, I'm here to help you activate the software.
4000000267	It's all the numbers and it's ten numbers.
4000000268	So this product you have has Windows Ten, right?
4000000269	Thank you for calling Microsoft, have a great day.
4000000270	That's why your order is a little bit delayed.
4000000271	There's nothing else we can do at this time.
4000000272	To get started, may I have your email address?
4000000273	Wasn't the refund issued on the twenty-eighth of February?
4000000274	We don't need a pass code to that email.
4000000275	We will get it solved as soon as possible.
4000000276	Alright then, I'll just log out of your computer now.
4000000277	Do you by any chance have any other phone number?
4000000278	Forty quid, a year for gold membership's not that bad.
4000000279	I understand, but first of all it's not our fault.
4000000280	I'm going to be here until six o'clock your time, sir.
4000000281	I'm sorry but this was connected to accounts and billing.
4000000282	No, just give me a few minutes.
4000000283	Then I'll just give you the download link.
4000000284	OK, let me look that up, give me a moment.
4000000285	OK, so how do you sign in to your computer?
4000000286	Sir, what exactly do you see on the screen now?
4000000287	You haven't done any update on your computer, right?
4000000288	It might automatically activate after the installation is complete.
4000000289	We cannot pay you back, an exception was already made.
4000000290	The refund was passed from our end.
4000000291	Check your email and also your phone for this verification code.
4000000292	Do not click anything ma'am, just stay on the line.
4000000293	Your package has been sent!
4000000294	Complete your purchase now and receive a ten percent discount!
4000000295	Your statement is now available on your account.
4000000296	You have been logged out of this session.
4000000297	Your order has been confirmed.
4000000298	You just received a deposit in your account.
4000000299	Waiting for Wi-Fi to continue download.
4000000300	Ok I will keep waiting then.